[
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        3
                    ], 
                    [
                        3, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UU"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MUU", 
        "correct": "MUUUU", 
        "incorrect": "UUMUU", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 0.9332469150938479, 
        "stimulus": 34, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ], 
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MI", 
        "correct": "MII", 
        "incorrect": "IMI", 
        "length": 3, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 0.894427190999916, 
        "stimulus": 0, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        4
                    ], 
                    [
                        4, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UUI"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MUUI", 
        "correct": "MUUIUUI", 
        "incorrect": "MUUUIUI", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 0.8284389107916664, 
        "stimulus": 33, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        3
                    ], 
                    [
                        3, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MU"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MMU", 
        "correct": "MMUMU", 
        "incorrect": "MMMUU", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 0.8484588119013364, 
        "stimulus": 5, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        4
                    ], 
                    [
                        4, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IUM"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MIUM", 
        "correct": "MIUMIUM", 
        "incorrect": "MIUIMUM", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 1.2723824796762224, 
        "stimulus": 40, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ], 
                    [
                        5, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UIIM"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MUIIM", 
        "correct": "MUIIMUIIM", 
        "incorrect": "MUIIUMIIM", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 0.9715144816249806, 
        "stimulus": 59, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        3
                    ], 
                    [
                        3, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MI"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MMI", 
        "correct": "MMIMI", 
        "incorrect": "MMMII", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 0.9445407812928889, 
        "stimulus": 32, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        3
                    ], 
                    [
                        3, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UI"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MUI", 
        "correct": "MUIUI", 
        "incorrect": "MUUII", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 1.0830546410468067, 
        "stimulus": 22, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        4
                    ], 
                    [
                        4, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IUI"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MIUI", 
        "correct": "MIUIIUI", 
        "incorrect": "MIUIUII", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 1.062642075085362, 
        "stimulus": 94, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ], 
                    [
                        5, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UMUM"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MUMUM", 
        "correct": "MUMUMUMUM", 
        "incorrect": "MUMUUMMUM", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 1.1438830300736103, 
        "stimulus": 114, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ], 
                    [
                        6, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UUMMI"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MUUMMI", 
        "correct": "MUUMMIUUMMI", 
        "incorrect": "MUUMMUIUMMI", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 0.8076413729373336, 
        "stimulus": 261, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ], 
                    [
                        6, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MMUMU"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MMMUMU", 
        "correct": "MMMUMUMMUMU", 
        "incorrect": "MMMUMMUMUMU", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 0.639941167854182, 
        "stimulus": 338, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ], 
                    [
                        6, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UMIMI"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MUMIMI", 
        "correct": "MUMIMIUMIMI", 
        "incorrect": "MUMIMUIMIMI", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 1.0514223976293466, 
        "stimulus": 268, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        4
                    ], 
                    [
                        4, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IIM"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MIIM", 
        "correct": "MIIMIIM", 
        "incorrect": "MIIIMIM", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 0.7902426659415323, 
        "stimulus": 38, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ], 
                    [
                        6, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IIMII"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MIIMII", 
        "correct": "MIIMIIIIMII", 
        "incorrect": "MIIMIIIMIII", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 1.0126043652214558, 
        "stimulus": 342, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ], 
                    [
                        6, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IMMIM"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MIMMIM", 
        "correct": "MIMMIMIMMIM", 
        "incorrect": "MIMMIIMMMIM", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 0.952676580746261, 
        "stimulus": 294, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ], 
                    [
                        5, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IIIU"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MIIIU", 
        "correct": "MIIIUIIIU", 
        "incorrect": "MIIIIUIIU", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 1.02220304447463, 
        "stimulus": 35, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ], 
                    [
                        6, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MMMIM"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MMMMIM", 
        "correct": "MMMMIMMMMIM", 
        "incorrect": "MMMMMIMMMIM", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 0.5882352941176471, 
        "stimulus": 260, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ], 
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MU", 
        "correct": "MUU", 
        "incorrect": "UMU", 
        "length": 3, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 1.2157101965150745, 
        "stimulus": 1, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ], 
                    [
                        5, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UIUM"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MUIUM", 
        "correct": "MUIUMUIUM", 
        "incorrect": "MUIUUMIUM", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 1.180153677553971, 
        "stimulus": 163, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        3
                    ], 
                    [
                        3, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IM"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MIM", 
        "correct": "MIMIM", 
        "incorrect": "MMIIM", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 0.9955349509114306, 
        "stimulus": 16, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ], 
                    [
                        5, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MMUM"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MMMUM", 
        "correct": "MMMUMMMUM", 
        "incorrect": "MMMMUMMUM", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 0.5714285714285715, 
        "stimulus": 53, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        4
                    ], 
                    [
                        4, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MUU"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MMUU", 
        "correct": "MMUUMUU", 
        "incorrect": "MMUMUUU", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 0.6499903419388702, 
        "stimulus": 26, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        3
                    ], 
                    [
                        3, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UM"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MUM", 
        "correct": "MUMUM", 
        "incorrect": "MUUMM", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 0.9354143466934853, 
        "stimulus": 2, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        3
                    ], 
                    [
                        3, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IU"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MIU", 
        "correct": "MIUIU", 
        "incorrect": "MIIUU", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 0.8845238015412742, 
        "stimulus": 47, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        4
                    ], 
                    [
                        4, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UIM"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MUIM", 
        "correct": "MUIMUIM", 
        "incorrect": "MUIUMIM", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 0.5749595745760689, 
        "stimulus": 23, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ], 
                    [
                        5, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MIMI"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MMIMI", 
        "correct": "MMIMIMIMI", 
        "incorrect": "MMIMMIIMI", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 0.8900610942191883, 
        "stimulus": 172, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        4
                    ], 
                    [
                        4, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MUI"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MMUI", 
        "correct": "MMUIMUI", 
        "incorrect": "MMUMIUI", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 0.9626779358903854, 
        "stimulus": 95, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        4
                    ], 
                    [
                        4, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MIU"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MMIU", 
        "correct": "MMIUMIU", 
        "incorrect": "MMIMUIU", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 0.7603016154886294, 
        "stimulus": 87, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ], 
                    [
                        6, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IMMMU"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MIMMMU", 
        "correct": "MIMMMUIMMMU", 
        "incorrect": "MIMMMIUMMMU", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 0.8773397725007015, 
        "stimulus": 79, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ], 
                    [
                        6, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MMMMU"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MMMMMU", 
        "correct": "MMMMMUMMMMU", 
        "incorrect": "MMMMMMUMMMU", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 0.7942141137664624, 
        "stimulus": 319, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        4
                    ], 
                    [
                        4, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MIM"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MMIM", 
        "correct": "MMIMMIM", 
        "incorrect": "MMMIMIM", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 0.4065578140908709, 
        "stimulus": 17, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ], 
                    [
                        6, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MUMUM"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MMUMUM", 
        "correct": "MMUMUMMUMUM", 
        "incorrect": "MMUMMUMUMUM", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 0.8106815465884636, 
        "stimulus": 251, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ], 
                    [
                        5, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IIII"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MIIII", 
        "correct": "MIIIIIIII", 
        "incorrect": "IIIIMIIII", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 0.8054503014635869, 
        "stimulus": 111, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ], 
                    [
                        5, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UUMM"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MUUMM", 
        "correct": "MUUMMUUMM", 
        "incorrect": "MUUMUMUMM", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 0.9052075116941658, 
        "stimulus": 14, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ], 
                    [
                        6, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IMUUI"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MIMUUI", 
        "correct": "MIMUUIIMUUI", 
        "incorrect": "MIMUUIMIUUI", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 1.1698510597781493, 
        "stimulus": 96, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ], 
                    [
                        5, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MUUM"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MMUUM", 
        "correct": "MMUUMMUUM", 
        "incorrect": "MMUMUMUUM", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 0.973279142585241, 
        "stimulus": 245, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        4
                    ], 
                    [
                        4, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UMM"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MUMM", 
        "correct": "MUMMUMM", 
        "incorrect": "MUMUMMM", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 0.853991925843794, 
        "stimulus": 49, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        3
                    ], 
                    [
                        3, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "II"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MII", 
        "correct": "MIIII", 
        "incorrect": "IMIII", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 0.8013471704107908, 
        "stimulus": 12, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        4
                    ], 
                    [
                        4, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IUU"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MIUU", 
        "correct": "MIUUIUU", 
        "incorrect": "MIUIUUU", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 0.77462538166327, 
        "stimulus": 36, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ], 
                    [
                        5, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UIUU"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MUIUU", 
        "correct": "MUIUUUIUU", 
        "incorrect": "MUIUUIUUU", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 0.930610358915714, 
        "stimulus": 108, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        4
                    ], 
                    [
                        4, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IMU"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MIMU", 
        "correct": "MIMUIMU", 
        "incorrect": "MIMIUMU", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 1.0607053859051483, 
        "stimulus": 66, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ], 
                    [
                        5, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UUUM"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MUUUM", 
        "correct": "MUUUMUUUM", 
        "incorrect": "MUUUUMUUM", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 0.7701378090302795, 
        "stimulus": 248, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ], 
                    [
                        5, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MIUU"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MMIUU", 
        "correct": "MMIUUMIUU", 
        "incorrect": "MMIUMUIUU", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 0.9482798605251253, 
        "stimulus": 50, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ], 
                    [
                        6, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MMUUI"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MMMUUI", 
        "correct": "MMMUUIMMUUI", 
        "incorrect": "MMMUUMIMUUI", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 0.8286616279957826, 
        "stimulus": 171, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        4
                    ], 
                    [
                        4, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MII"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MMII", 
        "correct": "MMIIMII", 
        "incorrect": "MMIMIII", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 0.8748335488053219, 
        "stimulus": 109, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ], 
                    [
                        5, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IMMI"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MIMMI", 
        "correct": "MIMMIIMMI", 
        "incorrect": "MIMMIMIMI", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 0.6860490254392339, 
        "stimulus": 15, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ], 
                    [
                        5, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IMII"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MIMII", 
        "correct": "MIMIIIMII", 
        "incorrect": "MIMIIMIII", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 1.1181605828774444, 
        "stimulus": 24, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ], 
                    [
                        5, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IIUU"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MIIUU", 
        "correct": "MIIUUIIUU", 
        "incorrect": "MIIUIUIUU", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 0.8798071006060447, 
        "stimulus": 129, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ], 
                    [
                        6, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UIIMM"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MUIIMM", 
        "correct": "MUIIMMUIIMM", 
        "incorrect": "MUIIMUMIIMM", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 1.1419367044374147, 
        "stimulus": 272, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        4
                    ], 
                    [
                        4, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UII"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MUII", 
        "correct": "MUIIUII", 
        "incorrect": "MUIUIII", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 0.77462538166327, 
        "stimulus": 107, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ], 
                    [
                        5, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MUIU"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MMUIU", 
        "correct": "MMUIUMUIU", 
        "incorrect": "MMUIMUUIU", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 1.2896765720252654, 
        "stimulus": 25, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ], 
                    [
                        5, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IMUM"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MIMUM", 
        "correct": "MIMUMIMUM", 
        "incorrect": "MIMUIMMUM", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 0.40406101782088427, 
        "stimulus": 9, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ], 
                    [
                        5, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IUMM"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MIUMM", 
        "correct": "MIUMMIUMM", 
        "incorrect": "MIUMIMUMM", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 1.1169248833726007, 
        "stimulus": 142, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ], 
                    [
                        6, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IIUUI"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MIIUUI", 
        "correct": "MIIUUIIIUUI", 
        "incorrect": "MIIUIUIIUUI", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 1.0801122467757382, 
        "stimulus": 182, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ], 
                    [
                        5, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IUII"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MIUII", 
        "correct": "MIUIIIUII", 
        "incorrect": "MIUIIUIII", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 0.9009591557227454, 
        "stimulus": 148, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ], 
                    [
                        5, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IUUM"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MIUUM", 
        "correct": "MIUUMIUUM", 
        "incorrect": "MIUUIMUUM", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 1.036892461981207, 
        "stimulus": 10, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ], 
                    [
                        5, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MIMU"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MMIMU", 
        "correct": "MMIMUMIMU", 
        "incorrect": "MMIMMUIMU", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 1.0162696723246754, 
        "stimulus": 124, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ], 
                    [
                        6, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IIUIU"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MIIUIU", 
        "correct": "MIIUIUIIUIU", 
        "incorrect": "MIIUIIUIUIU", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 1.0784442015390538, 
        "stimulus": 313, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ], 
                    [
                        5, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MIIU"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MMIIU", 
        "correct": "MMIIUMIIU", 
        "incorrect": "MMIIMUIIU", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 1.0505227465734759, 
        "stimulus": 56, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ], 
                    [
                        5, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UMMU"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MUMMU", 
        "correct": "MUMMUUMMU", 
        "incorrect": "MUMMUMUMU", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 0.810470386599485, 
        "stimulus": 200, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ], 
                    [
                        6, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IMUUM"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MIMUUM", 
        "correct": "MIMUUMIMUUM", 
        "incorrect": "MIMUUIMMUUM", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 0.9529603249400536, 
        "stimulus": 72, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ], 
                    [
                        5, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IUIU"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MIUIU", 
        "correct": "MIUIUIUIU", 
        "incorrect": "MIUIIUUIU", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 0.9651726484098984, 
        "stimulus": 208, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        4
                    ], 
                    [
                        4, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UUM"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MUUM", 
        "correct": "MUUMUUM", 
        "incorrect": "MUMUUUM", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 0.853991925843794, 
        "stimulus": 3, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ], 
                    [
                        5, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MMII"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MMMII", 
        "correct": "MMMIIMMII", 
        "incorrect": "MMMIMIMII", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 0.5072139297626351, 
        "stimulus": 141, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ], 
                    [
                        5, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UUUI"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MUUUI", 
        "correct": "MUUUIUUUI", 
        "incorrect": "MUUUUIUUI", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 1.0365401025024163, 
        "stimulus": 29, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ], 
                    [
                        6, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IIUUU"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MIIUUU", 
        "correct": "MIIUUUIIUUU", 
        "incorrect": "MIIUUIUIUUU", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 1.0827218367186453, 
        "stimulus": 128, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ], 
                    [
                        6, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IMMMM"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MIMMMM", 
        "correct": "MIMMMMIMMMM", 
        "incorrect": "MIMMMIMMMMM", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 1.0222676413622898, 
        "stimulus": 346, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ], 
                    [
                        5, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UMUI"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MUMUI", 
        "correct": "MUMUIUMUI", 
        "incorrect": "MUMUUIMUI", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 0.49868559913292554, 
        "stimulus": 18, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ], 
                    [
                        5, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MMIU"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MMMIU", 
        "correct": "MMMIUMMIU", 
        "incorrect": "MMMIMUMIU", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 1.0681342061036172, 
        "stimulus": 120, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ], 
                    [
                        6, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MUUMM"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MMUUMM", 
        "correct": "MMUUMMMUUMM", 
        "incorrect": "MMUMUMMUUMM", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 1.0428152420633214, 
        "stimulus": 306, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        4
                    ], 
                    [
                        4, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MMI"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MMMI", 
        "correct": "MMMIMMI", 
        "incorrect": "MMMMIMI", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 0.8143626384646174, 
        "stimulus": 20, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ], 
                    [
                        6, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IMMUI"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MIMMUI", 
        "correct": "MIMMUIIMMUI", 
        "incorrect": "MIMMUIMIMUI", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 0.8240344692698642, 
        "stimulus": 315, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ], 
                    [
                        6, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UIUII"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MUIUII", 
        "correct": "MUIUIIUIUII", 
        "incorrect": "MUIUIUIIUII", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 0.9149510182664502, 
        "stimulus": 318, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ], 
                    [
                        6, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UMMIM"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MUMMIM", 
        "correct": "MUMMIMUMMIM", 
        "incorrect": "MUMMIUMMMIM", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 1.0437134364090148, 
        "stimulus": 216, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ], 
                    [
                        6, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UIUUI"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MUIUUI", 
        "correct": "MUIUUIUIUUI", 
        "incorrect": "MUIUUUIIUUI", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 0.5890880225522961, 
        "stimulus": 227, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ], 
                    [
                        6, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IUUUM"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MIUUUM", 
        "correct": "MIUUUMIUUUM", 
        "incorrect": "MIUUUIMUUUM", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 1.1157514507289756, 
        "stimulus": 254, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ], 
                    [
                        6, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UIIII"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MUIIII", 
        "correct": "MUIIIIUIIII", 
        "incorrect": "MUIIIUIIIII", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 0.16637806616154063, 
        "stimulus": 259, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ], 
                    [
                        5, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IUIM"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MIUIM", 
        "correct": "MIUIMIUIM", 
        "incorrect": "MIUIIMUIM", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 0.8813544770895048, 
        "stimulus": 91, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ], 
                    [
                        5, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UUMU"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MUUMU", 
        "correct": "MUUMUUUMU", 
        "incorrect": "MUUUMUUMU", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 0.8089108323504375, 
        "stimulus": 75, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ], 
                    [
                        5, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UUUU"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MUUUU", 
        "correct": "MUUUUUUUU", 
        "incorrect": "UUUUMUUUU", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 0.85330113446066, 
        "stimulus": 158, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ], 
                    [
                        5, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MIMM"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MMIMM", 
        "correct": "MMIMMMIMM", 
        "incorrect": "MMMIMMIMM", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 0.8733432221698623, 
        "stimulus": 97, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ], 
                    [
                        6, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IUUMM"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MIUUMM", 
        "correct": "MIUUMMIUUMM", 
        "incorrect": "MIUUMIMUUMM", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 1.195197429574995, 
        "stimulus": 293, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ], 
                    [
                        6, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UIIUI"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MUIIUI", 
        "correct": "MUIIUIUIIUI", 
        "incorrect": "MUIIUUIIIUI", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 0.9893251041833303, 
        "stimulus": 166, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ], 
                    [
                        5, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MIUI"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MMIUI", 
        "correct": "MMIUIMIUI", 
        "incorrect": "MMIUMIIUI", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 1.1538701521858152, 
        "stimulus": 6, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ], 
                    [
                        5, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IUMI"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MIUMI", 
        "correct": "MIUMIIUMI", 
        "incorrect": "MIUMIUIMI", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 1.0196667331935152, 
        "stimulus": 192, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ], 
                    [
                        6, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UMMMI"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MUMMMI", 
        "correct": "MUMMMIUMMMI", 
        "incorrect": "MUMMMUIMMMI", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 0.9748233126083734, 
        "stimulus": 101, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ], 
                    [
                        5, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IIUI"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MIIUI", 
        "correct": "MIIUIIIUI", 
        "incorrect": "MIIIUIIUI", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 1.0183778123900031, 
        "stimulus": 98, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        4
                    ], 
                    [
                        4, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UUU"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MUUU", 
        "correct": "MUUUUUU", 
        "incorrect": "UUUMUUU", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 1.0410091877407412, 
        "stimulus": 116, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ], 
                    [
                        6, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UUUII"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MUUUII", 
        "correct": "MUUUIIUUUII", 
        "incorrect": "MUUUIUIUUII", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 1.0197194907793303, 
        "stimulus": 217, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ], 
                    [
                        5, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UUIM"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MUUIM", 
        "correct": "MUUIMUUIM", 
        "incorrect": "MUUIUMUIM", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 1.1698045763337215, 
        "stimulus": 123, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ], 
                    [
                        6, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MIMIM"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MMIMIM", 
        "correct": "MMIMIMMIMIM", 
        "incorrect": "MMIMMIMIMIM", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 1.2705366634129711, 
        "stimulus": 286, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ], 
                    [
                        6, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MMMUM"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MMMMUM", 
        "correct": "MMMMUMMMMUM", 
        "incorrect": "MMMMMUMMMUM", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 1.1117222162586495, 
        "stimulus": 287, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        4
                    ], 
                    [
                        4, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UMU"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MUMU", 
        "correct": "MUMUUMU", 
        "incorrect": "MUMUMUU", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 0.8506803305551318, 
        "stimulus": 42, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ], 
                    [
                        6, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IUUUI"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MIUUUI", 
        "correct": "MIUUUIIUUUI", 
        "incorrect": "MIUUUIUIUUI", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 0.8454673521133766, 
        "stimulus": 257, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        4
                    ], 
                    [
                        4, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MUM"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MMUM", 
        "correct": "MMUMMUM", 
        "incorrect": "MMMUMUM", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 0.9872956808325725, 
        "stimulus": 4, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ], 
                    [
                        6, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IMIIM"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MIMIIM", 
        "correct": "MIMIIMIMIIM", 
        "incorrect": "MIMIMIIMIIM", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 0.9522555630918869, 
        "stimulus": 206, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        4
                    ], 
                    [
                        4, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IIU"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MIIU", 
        "correct": "MIIUIIU", 
        "incorrect": "MIIIUIU", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 1.0525785234521312, 
        "stimulus": 21, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        4
                    ], 
                    [
                        4, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UIU"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MUIU", 
        "correct": "MUIUUIU", 
        "incorrect": "MUIUIUU", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 1.0488205349656072, 
        "stimulus": 64, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ], 
                    [
                        6, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IIMIM"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MIIMIM", 
        "correct": "MIIMIMIIMIM", 
        "incorrect": "MIIMIIMIMIM", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 1.0784748846651182, 
        "stimulus": 232, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ], 
                    [
                        6, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UMUIM"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MUMUIM", 
        "correct": "MUMUIMUMUIM", 
        "incorrect": "MUMUIUMMUIM", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 1.01357275658723, 
        "stimulus": 144, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ], 
                    [
                        6, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IMIII"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MIMIII", 
        "correct": "MIMIIIIMIII", 
        "incorrect": "MIMIIIMIIII", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 0.5123715831144574, 
        "stimulus": 335, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        4
                    ], 
                    [
                        4, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MMU"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MMMU", 
        "correct": "MMMUMMU", 
        "incorrect": "MMMMUMU", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 0.7534113456056949, 
        "stimulus": 7, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ], 
                    [
                        6, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MMIII"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MMMIII", 
        "correct": "MMMIIIMMIII", 
        "incorrect": "MMMIIMIMIII", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 1.1769082579435408, 
        "stimulus": 277, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ], 
                    [
                        6, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UMIMM"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MUMIMM", 
        "correct": "MUMIMMUMIMM", 
        "incorrect": "MUMIMUMMIMM", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 0.9285926784650769, 
        "stimulus": 226, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ], 
                    [
                        5, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MUMU"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MMUMU", 
        "correct": "MMUMUMUMU", 
        "incorrect": "MMUMMUUMU", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 0.6102555338368373, 
        "stimulus": 119, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ], 
                    [
                        6, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MIIMU"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MMIIMU", 
        "correct": "MMIIMUMIIMU", 
        "incorrect": "MMIIMMUIIMU", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 0.9121270322305374, 
        "stimulus": 243, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        4
                    ], 
                    [
                        4, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "III"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MIII", 
        "correct": "MIIIIII", 
        "incorrect": "IIIMIII", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 1.0410091877407412, 
        "stimulus": 70, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ], 
                    [
                        6, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IUIIM"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MIUIIM", 
        "correct": "MIUIIMIUIIM", 
        "incorrect": "MIUIIIMUIIM", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 1.0531008012077026, 
        "stimulus": 278, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ], 
                    [
                        6, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IUIUM"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MIUIUM", 
        "correct": "MIUIUMIUIUM", 
        "incorrect": "MIUIUIMUIUM", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 1.287917874216571, 
        "stimulus": 30, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ], 
                    [
                        6, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IIUMU"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MIIUMU", 
        "correct": "MIIUMUIIUMU", 
        "incorrect": "MIIUMIUIUMU", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 1.1094422743291996, 
        "stimulus": 273, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ], 
                    [
                        6, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MMIUM"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MMMIUM", 
        "correct": "MMMIUMMMIUM", 
        "incorrect": "MMMIMUMMIUM", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 1.0500141074065907, 
        "stimulus": 295, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ], 
                    [
                        6, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UUIMU"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MUUIMU", 
        "correct": "MUUIMUUUIMU", 
        "incorrect": "MUUIUMUUIMU", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 0.8892403376919635, 
        "stimulus": 184, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ], 
                    [
                        6, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MMUII"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MMMUII", 
        "correct": "MMMUIIMMUII", 
        "incorrect": "MMMUIMIMUII", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 1.0255900940597864, 
        "stimulus": 84, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        4
                    ], 
                    [
                        4, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IMM"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MIMM", 
        "correct": "MIMMIMM", 
        "incorrect": "MIMIMMM", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 0.853991925843794, 
        "stimulus": 11, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ], 
                    [
                        5, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UUMI"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MUUMI", 
        "correct": "MUUMIUUMI", 
        "incorrect": "MUUMUIUMI", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 0.9705779703463917, 
        "stimulus": 138, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ], 
                    [
                        6, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UMIIU"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MUMIIU", 
        "correct": "MUMIIUUMIIU", 
        "incorrect": "MUMIIUMUIIU", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 1.1854980442418697, 
        "stimulus": 355, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ], 
                    [
                        5, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MMUU"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MMMUU", 
        "correct": "MMMUUMMUU", 
        "incorrect": "MMMUMUMUU", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 0.6950045155736072, 
        "stimulus": 113, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ], 
                    [
                        5, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UIUI"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MUIUI", 
        "correct": "MUIUIUIUI", 
        "incorrect": "MUIUUIIUI", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 1.0209669687469625, 
        "stimulus": 130, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ], 
                    [
                        5, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MUUU"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MMUUU", 
        "correct": "MMUUUMUUU", 
        "incorrect": "MMUUMUUUU", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 0.7567721464434676, 
        "stimulus": 19, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ], 
                    [
                        5, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IUUU"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MIUUU", 
        "correct": "MIUUUIUUU", 
        "incorrect": "MIUUIUUUU", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 1.0853504286192475, 
        "stimulus": 78, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ], 
                    [
                        6, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IMUMU"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MIMUMU", 
        "correct": "MIMUMUIMUMU", 
        "incorrect": "MIMUMIUMUMU", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 0.9345525097370078, 
        "stimulus": 8, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ], 
                    [
                        5, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IUUI"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MIUUI", 
        "correct": "MIUUIIUUI", 
        "incorrect": "MIUUIUIUI", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 1.051029995880115, 
        "stimulus": 229, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ], 
                    [
                        6, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MIIUI"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MMIIUI", 
        "correct": "MMIIUIMIIUI", 
        "incorrect": "MMIIUMIIIUI", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 0.9787111911843174, 
        "stimulus": 344, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ], 
                    [
                        6, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MMIMI"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MMMIMI", 
        "correct": "MMMIMIMMIMI", 
        "incorrect": "MMMIMMIMIMI", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 1.032668476251269, 
        "stimulus": 140, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ], 
                    [
                        6, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IMUIM"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MIMUIM", 
        "correct": "MIMUIMIMUIM", 
        "incorrect": "MIMUIIMMUIM", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 1.1290611618176758, 
        "stimulus": 80, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ], 
                    [
                        5, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UIIU"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MUIIU", 
        "correct": "MUIIUUIIU", 
        "incorrect": "MUIIUIUIU", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 0.4285714285714286, 
        "stimulus": 52, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ], 
                    [
                        5, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IIUM"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MIIUM", 
        "correct": "MIIUMIIUM", 
        "incorrect": "MIIUIMIUM", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 1.0897204729868397, 
        "stimulus": 69, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ], 
                    [
                        6, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IMUMM"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MIMUMM", 
        "correct": "MIMUMMIMUMM", 
        "incorrect": "MIMUMIMMUMM", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 1.0263909088704886, 
        "stimulus": 331, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ], 
                    [
                        6, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MMUIM"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MMMUIM", 
        "correct": "MMMUIMMMUIM", 
        "incorrect": "MMMUMIMMUIM", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 0.876674199604295, 
        "stimulus": 27, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ], 
                    [
                        6, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UUUIM"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MUUUIM", 
        "correct": "MUUUIMUUUIM", 
        "incorrect": "MUUUIUMUUIM", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 0.8522961470217956, 
        "stimulus": 157, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ], 
                    [
                        5, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IMMM"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MIMMM", 
        "correct": "MIMMMIMMM", 
        "incorrect": "MIMMIMMMM", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 0.812826898781965, 
        "stimulus": 46, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ], 
                    [
                        6, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UUMUU"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MUUMUU", 
        "correct": "MUUMUUUUMUU", 
        "incorrect": "MUUMUUMUUUU", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 0.8098799258585763, 
        "stimulus": 209, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ], 
                    [
                        6, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UIUMI"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MUIUMI", 
        "correct": "MUIUMIUIUMI", 
        "incorrect": "MUIUMUIIUMI", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 1.0417183521040028, 
        "stimulus": 68, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ], 
                    [
                        6, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MMIUI"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MMMIUI", 
        "correct": "MMMIUIMMIUI", 
        "incorrect": "MMMIUMIMIUI", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 1.0891051494879738, 
        "stimulus": 225, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ], 
                    [
                        6, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UMUMM"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MUMUMM", 
        "correct": "MUMUMMUMUMM", 
        "incorrect": "MUMUMUMMUMM", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 0.5335802383711719, 
        "stimulus": 215, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ], 
                    [
                        6, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MMMII"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MMMMII", 
        "correct": "MMMMIIMMMII", 
        "incorrect": "MMMMIMIMMII", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 0.7937090452066844, 
        "stimulus": 173, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ], 
                    [
                        6, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MUMMI"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MMUMMI", 
        "correct": "MMUMMIMUMMI", 
        "incorrect": "MMUMMMIUMMI", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 0.7106021636830036, 
        "stimulus": 246, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ], 
                    [
                        6, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MIIMI"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MMIIMI", 
        "correct": "MMIIMIMIIMI", 
        "incorrect": "MMIIMMIIIMI", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 0.8975174980450787, 
        "stimulus": 296, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ], 
                    [
                        5, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UIMU"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MUIMU", 
        "correct": "MUIMUUIMU", 
        "incorrect": "MUIMUIUMU", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 0.8554033290001094, 
        "stimulus": 136, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ], 
                    [
                        6, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IIIUM"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MIIIUM", 
        "correct": "MIIIUMIIIUM", 
        "incorrect": "MIIIUIMIIUM", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 1.120768256229343, 
        "stimulus": 187, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ], 
                    [
                        6, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MIIIM"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MMIIIM", 
        "correct": "MMIIIMMIIIM", 
        "incorrect": "MMIIMIMIIIM", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 1.0197194907793303, 
        "stimulus": 332, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ], 
                    [
                        5, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MIIM"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MMIIM", 
        "correct": "MMIIMMIIM", 
        "incorrect": "MMIMIMIIM", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 0.9832466954600977, 
        "stimulus": 90, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ], 
                    [
                        5, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MUMI"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MMUMI", 
        "correct": "MMUMIMUMI", 
        "incorrect": "MMUMMIUMI", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 0.9602959804162977, 
        "stimulus": 178, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ], 
                    [
                        6, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MIUUI"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MMIUUI", 
        "correct": "MMIUUIMIUUI", 
        "incorrect": "MMIUUMIIUUI", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 1.1215488993253275, 
        "stimulus": 198, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ], 
                    [
                        6, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IMUMI"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MIMUMI", 
        "correct": "MIMUMIIMUMI", 
        "incorrect": "MIMUMIMIUMI", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 1.1121741215480703, 
        "stimulus": 89, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ], 
                    [
                        5, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IUMU"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MIUMU", 
        "correct": "MIUMUIUMU", 
        "incorrect": "MIUMIUUMU", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 0.8832404345242945, 
        "stimulus": 88, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ], 
                    [
                        5, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MMMU"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MMMMU", 
        "correct": "MMMMUMMMU", 
        "incorrect": "MMMMMUMMU", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 0.6398740309703185, 
        "stimulus": 104, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ], 
                    [
                        6, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UUMIU"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MUUMIU", 
        "correct": "MUUMIUUUMIU", 
        "incorrect": "MUUMUIUUMIU", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 0.785053193932573, 
        "stimulus": 327, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ], 
                    [
                        6, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IMMMI"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MIMMMI", 
        "correct": "MIMMMIIMMMI", 
        "incorrect": "MIMMMIMIMMI", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 0.6933617576697081, 
        "stimulus": 256, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ], 
                    [
                        6, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IUUII"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MIUUII", 
        "correct": "MIUUIIIUUII", 
        "incorrect": "MIUUIIUIUII", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 1.1499392478016255, 
        "stimulus": 181, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ], 
                    [
                        5, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IIIM"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MIIIM", 
        "correct": "MIIIMIIIM", 
        "incorrect": "MIIMIIIIM", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 1.0418414832046894, 
        "stimulus": 118, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ], 
                    [
                        5, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UMMI"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MUMMI", 
        "correct": "MUMMIUMMI", 
        "incorrect": "MUMMUIMMI", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 1.0455404350250452, 
        "stimulus": 185, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ], 
                    [
                        6, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MIUMM"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MMIUMM", 
        "correct": "MMIUMMMIUMM", 
        "incorrect": "MMIUMMIMUMM", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 1.0936161675597669, 
        "stimulus": 320, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ], 
                    [
                        6, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MIMUU"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MMIMUU", 
        "correct": "MMIMUUMIMUU", 
        "incorrect": "MMIMUMUIMUU", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 0.9608195710405304, 
        "stimulus": 290, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ], 
                    [
                        5, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MUIM"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MMUIM", 
        "correct": "MMUIMMUIM", 
        "incorrect": "MMUMIMUIM", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 1.1283528044153317, 
        "stimulus": 137, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ], 
                    [
                        6, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UMIMU"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MUMIMU", 
        "correct": "MUMIMUUMIMU", 
        "incorrect": "MUMIMUMUIMU", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 1.0100166261461143, 
        "stimulus": 264, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ], 
                    [
                        6, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UIMUU"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MUIMUU", 
        "correct": "MUIMUUUIMUU", 
        "incorrect": "MUIMUUIUMUU", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 1.1430928306394577, 
        "stimulus": 265, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ], 
                    [
                        5, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IMUU"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MIMUU", 
        "correct": "MIMUUIMUU", 
        "incorrect": "MIMUIUMUU", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 1.0174144137051262, 
        "stimulus": 43, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ], 
                    [
                        6, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UIUUU"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MUIUUU", 
        "correct": "MUIUUUUIUUU", 
        "incorrect": "MUIUUUIUUUU", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 0.8744016683677903, 
        "stimulus": 103, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ], 
                    [
                        5, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IIMU"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MIIMU", 
        "correct": "MIIMUIIMU", 
        "incorrect": "MIIMIUIMU", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 0.35846668228426204, 
        "stimulus": 164, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ], 
                    [
                        5, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UMMM"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MUMMM", 
        "correct": "MUMMMUMMM", 
        "incorrect": "MUMMUMMMM", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 0.7567721464434676, 
        "stimulus": 39, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ], 
                    [
                        5, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UIII"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MUIII", 
        "correct": "MUIIIUIII", 
        "incorrect": "MUIIUIIII", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 0.8657929923884429, 
        "stimulus": 127, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ], 
                    [
                        5, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UIMI"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MUIMI", 
        "correct": "MUIMIUIMI", 
        "incorrect": "MUIMUIIMI", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 0.9052075116941658, 
        "stimulus": 233, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ], 
                    [
                        6, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MIIII"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MMIIII", 
        "correct": "MMIIIIMIIII", 
        "incorrect": "MMIIIMIIIII", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 1.0312533215193715, 
        "stimulus": 63, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ], 
                    [
                        6, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UIMMM"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MUIMMM", 
        "correct": "MUIMMMUIMMM", 
        "incorrect": "MUIMMUMIMMM", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 1.2173656543356042, 
        "stimulus": 284, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ], 
                    [
                        5, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IIMI"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MIIMI", 
        "correct": "MIIMIIIMI", 
        "incorrect": "MIIIMIIMI", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 0.7871275569304601, 
        "stimulus": 221, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ], 
                    [
                        6, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UIIUM"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MUIIUM", 
        "correct": "MUIIUMUIIUM", 
        "incorrect": "MUIIUUMIIUM", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 1.065095716059841, 
        "stimulus": 345, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ], 
                    [
                        5, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UIMM"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MUIMM", 
        "correct": "MUIMMUIMM", 
        "incorrect": "MUIMUMIMM", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 0.8963865003505759, 
        "stimulus": 183, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ], 
                    [
                        6, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UIMUM"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MUIMUM", 
        "correct": "MUIMUMUIMUM", 
        "incorrect": "MUIMUUMIMUM", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 0.9747452831642422, 
        "stimulus": 322, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ], 
                    [
                        6, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MMMMI"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MMMMMI", 
        "correct": "MMMMMIMMMMI", 
        "incorrect": "MMMMMMIMMMI", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 0.3720326659021623, 
        "stimulus": 247, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ], 
                    [
                        6, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MUUMU"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MMUUMU", 
        "correct": "MMUUMUMUUMU", 
        "incorrect": "MMUUMMUUUMU", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 0.8567627051341599, 
        "stimulus": 126, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ], 
                    [
                        5, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MIUM"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MMIUM", 
        "correct": "MMIUMMIUM", 
        "incorrect": "MMIMUMIUM", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 1.0398072458947851, 
        "stimulus": 161, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ], 
                    [
                        5, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UMIM"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MUMIM", 
        "correct": "MUMIMUMIM", 
        "incorrect": "MUMIUMMIM", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 0.8554033290001094, 
        "stimulus": 202, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ], 
                    [
                        6, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IMMUU"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MIMMUU", 
        "correct": "MIMMUUIMMUU", 
        "incorrect": "MIMMUIUMMUU", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 0.9681614007824936, 
        "stimulus": 282, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ], 
                    [
                        6, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IMUUU"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MIMUUU", 
        "correct": "MIMUUUIMUUU", 
        "incorrect": "MIMUUIUMUUU", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 1.1016820315052576, 
        "stimulus": 190, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ], 
                    [
                        5, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IMUI"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MIMUI", 
        "correct": "MIMUIIMUI", 
        "incorrect": "MIMUIMIUI", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 1.0219073219486317, 
        "stimulus": 151, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ], 
                    [
                        5, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UUIU"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MUUIU", 
        "correct": "MUUIUUUIU", 
        "incorrect": "MUUUIUUIU", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 0.8058235592147427, 
        "stimulus": 194, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        4
                    ], 
                    [
                        4, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UMI"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MUMI", 
        "correct": "MUMIUMI", 
        "incorrect": "MUMUIMI", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 1.1064671117603078, 
        "stimulus": 13, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ], 
                    [
                        5, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UMIU"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MUMIU", 
        "correct": "MUMIUUMIU", 
        "incorrect": "MUMIUMUIU", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 1.036892461981207, 
        "stimulus": 275, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ], 
                    [
                        5, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IIMM"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MIIMM", 
        "correct": "MIIMMIIMM", 
        "incorrect": "MIIMIMIMM", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 0.9496105553006412, 
        "stimulus": 235, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ], 
                    [
                        6, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MUIII"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MMUIII", 
        "correct": "MMUIIIMUIII", 
        "incorrect": "MMUIIMIUIII", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 0.9367195802059328, 
        "stimulus": 253, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ], 
                    [
                        5, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UUII"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MUUII", 
        "correct": "MUUIIUUII", 
        "incorrect": "MUUIUIUII", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 1.0224577192371544, 
        "stimulus": 204, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ], 
                    [
                        6, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MUIMM"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MMUIMM", 
        "correct": "MMUIMMMUIMM", 
        "incorrect": "MMUIMMUMIMM", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 0.7392414533699035, 
        "stimulus": 212, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        4
                    ], 
                    [
                        4, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IMI"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MIMI", 
        "correct": "MIMIIMI", 
        "incorrect": "MIMIMII", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 1.146991951067869, 
        "stimulus": 48, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ], 
                    [
                        6, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MUMUU"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MMUMUU", 
        "correct": "MMUMUUMUMUU", 
        "incorrect": "MMUMUMUUMUU", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 1.0237032353257913, 
        "stimulus": 228, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ], 
                    [
                        6, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MIMIU"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MMIMIU", 
        "correct": "MMIMIUMIMIU", 
        "incorrect": "MMIMIMUIMIU", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 0.4864533288173337, 
        "stimulus": 305, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ], 
                    [
                        6, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IIMUM"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MIIMUM", 
        "correct": "MIIMUMIIMUM", 
        "incorrect": "MIIMUIMIMUM", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 0.867327362554837, 
        "stimulus": 340, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ], 
                    [
                        5, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MIII"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MMIII", 
        "correct": "MMIIIMIII", 
        "incorrect": "MMIIMIIII", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 0.8926167514052018, 
        "stimulus": 54, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ], 
                    [
                        6, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UMMII"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MUMMII", 
        "correct": "MUMMIIUMMII", 
        "incorrect": "MUMMIUIMMII", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 1.1816225136980687, 
        "stimulus": 196, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ], 
                    [
                        6, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IIUII"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MIIUII", 
        "correct": "MIIUIIIIUII", 
        "incorrect": "MIIUIIUIIII", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 0.862467461693339, 
        "stimulus": 191, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ], 
                    [
                        6, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UMIUU"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MUMIUU", 
        "correct": "MUMIUUUMIUU", 
        "incorrect": "MUMIUUMUIUU", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 1.1682836565033976, 
        "stimulus": 81, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ], 
                    [
                        6, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MUUMI"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MMUUMI", 
        "correct": "MMUUMIMUUMI", 
        "incorrect": "MMUUMMIUUMI", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 1.0828782766815959, 
        "stimulus": 214, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ], 
                    [
                        6, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IIIMU"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MIIIMU", 
        "correct": "MIIIMUIIIMU", 
        "incorrect": "MIIIMIUIIMU", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 0.8667113628873488, 
        "stimulus": 239, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ], 
                    [
                        6, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IMIUI"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MIMIUI", 
        "correct": "MIMIUIIMIUI", 
        "incorrect": "MIMIUIMIIUI", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 0.9494311641066914, 
        "stimulus": 162, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ], 
                    [
                        6, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UMIUM"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MUMIUM", 
        "correct": "MUMIUMUMIUM", 
        "incorrect": "MUMIUUMMIUM", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 1.1947504879197126, 
        "stimulus": 74, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ], 
                    [
                        6, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MUMMM"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MMUMMM", 
        "correct": "MMUMMMMUMMM", 
        "incorrect": "MMUMMMUMMMM", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 0.598424077608542, 
        "stimulus": 234, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ], 
                    [
                        6, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IIUIM"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MIIUIM", 
        "correct": "MIIUIMIIUIM", 
        "incorrect": "MIIUIIMIUIM", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 1.1786349780951346, 
        "stimulus": 189, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ], 
                    [
                        6, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IMIUM"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MIMIUM", 
        "correct": "MIMIUMIMIUM", 
        "incorrect": "MIMIUIMMIUM", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 1.1096322598045876, 
        "stimulus": 100, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ], 
                    [
                        6, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IIMUU"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MIIMUU", 
        "correct": "MIIMUUIIMUU", 
        "incorrect": "MIIMUIUIMUU", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 1.1592222431566166, 
        "stimulus": 222, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ], 
                    [
                        6, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UIMIM"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MUIMIM", 
        "correct": "MUIMIMUIMIM", 
        "incorrect": "MUIMIUMIMIM", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 0.6331926592132012, 
        "stimulus": 356, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ], 
                    [
                        6, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UUMII"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MUUMII", 
        "correct": "MUUMIIUUMII", 
        "incorrect": "MUUMIUIUMII", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 1.0203776572160246, 
        "stimulus": 99, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ], 
                    [
                        6, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UIUMU"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MUIUMU", 
        "correct": "MUIUMUUIUMU", 
        "incorrect": "MUIUMUIUUMU", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 1.0072405360424304, 
        "stimulus": 297, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ], 
                    [
                        6, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MMIMM"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MMMIMM", 
        "correct": "MMMIMMMMIMM", 
        "incorrect": "MMMMIMMMIMM", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 0.47058823529411764, 
        "stimulus": 312, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ], 
                    [
                        6, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IMIMU"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MIMIMU", 
        "correct": "MIMIMUIMIMU", 
        "incorrect": "MIMIMIUMIMU", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 0.5893755040007015, 
        "stimulus": 343, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ], 
                    [
                        6, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UMMUU"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MUMMUU", 
        "correct": "MUMMUUUMMUU", 
        "incorrect": "MUMMUUMUMUU", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 1.0801122467757382, 
        "stimulus": 139, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ], 
                    [
                        6, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MIUIU"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MMIUIU", 
        "correct": "MMIUIUMIUIU", 
        "incorrect": "MMIUIMUIUIU", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 1.098138019855926, 
        "stimulus": 309, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ], 
                    [
                        6, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UMMUM"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MUMMUM", 
        "correct": "MUMMUMUMMUM", 
        "incorrect": "MUMMUUMMMUM", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 0.952676580746261, 
        "stimulus": 329, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ], 
                    [
                        6, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MUMIM"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MMUMIM", 
        "correct": "MMUMIMMUMIM", 
        "incorrect": "MMUMMIMUMIM", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 0.8530834928063046, 
        "stimulus": 159, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ], 
                    [
                        5, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MUMM"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MMUMM", 
        "correct": "MMUMMMUMM", 
        "incorrect": "MMMUMMUMM", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 0.9098034079430827, 
        "stimulus": 195, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ], 
                    [
                        6, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UUMMU"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MUUMMU", 
        "correct": "MUUMMUUUMMU", 
        "incorrect": "MUUMUMUUMMU", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 0.8688830442180399, 
        "stimulus": 324, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ], 
                    [
                        5, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UMII"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MUMII", 
        "correct": "MUMIIUMII", 
        "incorrect": "MUMIUIMII", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 0.3829445266040947, 
        "stimulus": 154, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ], 
                    [
                        6, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IUUMI"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MIUUMI", 
        "correct": "MIUUMIIUUMI", 
        "incorrect": "MIUUMIUIUMI", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 1.1043406463632095, 
        "stimulus": 197, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ], 
                    [
                        6, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UIMIU"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MUIMIU", 
        "correct": "MUIMIUUIMIU", 
        "incorrect": "MUIMIUIUMIU", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 0.8682391015779582, 
        "stimulus": 321, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ], 
                    [
                        5, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MMMI"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MMMMI", 
        "correct": "MMMMIMMMI", 
        "incorrect": "MMMMMIMMI", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 0.719394866921348, 
        "stimulus": 37, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ], 
                    [
                        5, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MMIM"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MMMIM", 
        "correct": "MMMIMMMIM", 
        "incorrect": "MMMMIMMIM", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 1.0240724505434127, 
        "stimulus": 169, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ], 
                    [
                        6, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UMIIM"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MUMIIM", 
        "correct": "MUMIIMUMIIM", 
        "incorrect": "MUMIIUMMIIM", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 1.036447464325991, 
        "stimulus": 203, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ], 
                    [
                        6, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MIUII"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MMIUII", 
        "correct": "MMIUIIMIUII", 
        "incorrect": "MMIUIMIIUII", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 1.1524345495564041, 
        "stimulus": 175, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ], 
                    [
                        6, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IUIUI"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MIUIUI", 
        "correct": "MIUIUIIUIUI", 
        "incorrect": "MIUIUIUIIUI", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 1.2005277870771296, 
        "stimulus": 60, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ], 
                    [
                        6, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UUIUM"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MUUIUM", 
        "correct": "MUUIUMUUIUM", 
        "incorrect": "MUUIUUMUIUM", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 1.01227455384158, 
        "stimulus": 303, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ], 
                    [
                        6, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IIMMU"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MIIMMU", 
        "correct": "MIIMMUIIMMU", 
        "incorrect": "MIIMMIUIMMU", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 1.0048712806450641, 
        "stimulus": 150, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ], 
                    [
                        6, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UUUMM"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MUUUMM", 
        "correct": "MUUUMMUUUMM", 
        "incorrect": "MUUUMUMUUMM", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 1.1319772693560055, 
        "stimulus": 311, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ], 
                    [
                        6, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IUMUU"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MIUMUU", 
        "correct": "MIUMUUIUMUU", 
        "incorrect": "MIUMUIUUMUU", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 1.0321408563985066, 
        "stimulus": 122, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ], 
                    [
                        6, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MMIMU"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MMMIMU", 
        "correct": "MMMIMUMMIMU", 
        "incorrect": "MMMIMMUMIMU", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 0.5821691816243698, 
        "stimulus": 347, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ], 
                    [
                        6, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MMMUU"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MMMMUU", 
        "correct": "MMMMUUMMMUU", 
        "incorrect": "MMMMUMUMMUU", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 1.0146859510346813, 
        "stimulus": 210, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ], 
                    [
                        6, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UMMMM"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MUMMMM", 
        "correct": "MUMMMMUMMMM", 
        "incorrect": "MUMMMUMMMMM", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 0.3529411764705882, 
        "stimulus": 304, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ], 
                    [
                        6, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IIIIM"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MIIIIM", 
        "correct": "MIIIIMIIIIM", 
        "incorrect": "MIIIIIMIIIM", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 0.8848871077453577, 
        "stimulus": 165, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ], 
                    [
                        6, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IUMMI"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MIUMMI", 
        "correct": "MIUMMIIUMMI", 
        "incorrect": "MIUMMIUIMMI", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 1.1816225136980687, 
        "stimulus": 62, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ], 
                    [
                        6, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UIMMI"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MUIMMI", 
        "correct": "MUIMMIUIMMI", 
        "incorrect": "MUIMMUIIMMI", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 0.5882352941176471, 
        "stimulus": 258, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ], 
                    [
                        5, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UMUU"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MUMUU", 
        "correct": "MUMUUUMUU", 
        "incorrect": "MUMUUMUUU", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 1.0165301229199895, 
        "stimulus": 102, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ], 
                    [
                        6, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IMUIU"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MIMUIU", 
        "correct": "MIMUIUIMUIU", 
        "incorrect": "MIMUIIUMUIU", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 0.8844338208091115, 
        "stimulus": 236, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ], 
                    [
                        6, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IMIIU"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MIMIIU", 
        "correct": "MIMIIUIMIIU", 
        "incorrect": "MIMIIIUMIIU", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 1.0760946114691168, 
        "stimulus": 276, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ], 
                    [
                        6, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IUUMU"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MIUUMU", 
        "correct": "MIUUMUIUUMU", 
        "incorrect": "MIUUMIUUUMU", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 0.8050982647274537, 
        "stimulus": 337, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ], 
                    [
                        5, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IMMU"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MIMMU", 
        "correct": "MIMMUIMMU", 
        "incorrect": "MIMMIUMMU", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 0.9634425260001489, 
        "stimulus": 266, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ], 
                    [
                        6, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MUIIU"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MMUIIU", 
        "correct": "MMUIIUMUIIU", 
        "incorrect": "MMUIIMUUIIU", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 1.127097827701709, 
        "stimulus": 125, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ], 
                    [
                        5, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IMIU"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MIMIU", 
        "correct": "MIMIUIMIU", 
        "incorrect": "MIMIIUMIU", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 1.0610971810882588, 
        "stimulus": 58, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ], 
                    [
                        5, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IMIM"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MIMIM", 
        "correct": "MIMIMIMIM", 
        "incorrect": "MIMIIMMIM", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 1.0028021535188378, 
        "stimulus": 55, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ], 
                    [
                        6, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IUIMU"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MIUIMU", 
        "correct": "MIUIMUIUIMU", 
        "incorrect": "MIUIMIUUIMU", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 1.1969736697311169, 
        "stimulus": 314, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ], 
                    [
                        6, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UMUII"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MUMUII", 
        "correct": "MUMUIIUMUII", 
        "incorrect": "MUMUIUIMUII", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 0.9290922252483999, 
        "stimulus": 44, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ], 
                    [
                        6, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MIIIU"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MMIIIU", 
        "correct": "MMIIIUMIIIU", 
        "incorrect": "MMIIIMUIIIU", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 1.098138019855926, 
        "stimulus": 242, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ], 
                    [
                        6, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UUIUU"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MUUIUU", 
        "correct": "MUUIUUUUIUU", 
        "incorrect": "MUUIUUUIUUU", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 0.6705163034793846, 
        "stimulus": 170, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ], 
                    [
                        6, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IMUII"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MIMUII", 
        "correct": "MIMUIIIMUII", 
        "incorrect": "MIMUIIMIUII", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 0.997880930625958, 
        "stimulus": 77, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ], 
                    [
                        5, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MUII"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MMUII", 
        "correct": "MMUIIMUII", 
        "incorrect": "MMUIMIUII", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 1.0270042913484552, 
        "stimulus": 174, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ], 
                    [
                        6, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UUIIM"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MUUIIM", 
        "correct": "MUUIIMUUIIM", 
        "incorrect": "MUUIIUMUIIM", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 1.238950155240375, 
        "stimulus": 289, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ], 
                    [
                        6, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MUUUU"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MMUUUU", 
        "correct": "MMUUUUMUUUU", 
        "incorrect": "MMUUUMUUUUU", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 0.9153891936710609, 
        "stimulus": 252, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ], 
                    [
                        6, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UIUUM"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MUIUUM", 
        "correct": "MUIUUMUIUUM", 
        "incorrect": "MUIUUUMIUUM", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 1.0531008012077026, 
        "stimulus": 85, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ], 
                    [
                        5, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MUUI"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MMUUI", 
        "correct": "MMUUIMUUI", 
        "incorrect": "MMUUMIUUI", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 1.0750732395495508, 
        "stimulus": 153, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ], 
                    [
                        6, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UMUUM"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MUMUUM", 
        "correct": "MUMUUMUMUUM", 
        "incorrect": "MUMUMUUMUUM", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 0.8106815465884636, 
        "stimulus": 334, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ], 
                    [
                        6, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UIUIU"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MUIUIU", 
        "correct": "MUIUIUUIUIU", 
        "incorrect": "MUIUIUIUUIU", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 0.8725989039679953, 
        "stimulus": 92, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ], 
                    [
                        6, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MUIUI"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MMUIUI", 
        "correct": "MMUIUIMUIUI", 
        "incorrect": "MMUIUMIUIUI", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 1.151503731403548, 
        "stimulus": 262, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ], 
                    [
                        6, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MIMMI"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MMIMMI", 
        "correct": "MMIMMIMIMMI", 
        "incorrect": "MMIMMMIIMMI", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 0.9271535708965079, 
        "stimulus": 205, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ], 
                    [
                        6, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UMIUI"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MUMIUI", 
        "correct": "MUMIUIUMIUI", 
        "incorrect": "MUMIUUIMIUI", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 0.8851925817930297, 
        "stimulus": 51, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ], 
                    [
                        5, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MMUI"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MMMUI", 
        "correct": "MMMUIMMUI", 
        "incorrect": "MMMUMIMUI", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 1.0884710733058378, 
        "stimulus": 121, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ], 
                    [
                        6, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MMMUI"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MMMMUI", 
        "correct": "MMMMUIMMMUI", 
        "incorrect": "MMMMUMIMMUI", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 0.718463371031048, 
        "stimulus": 310, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ], 
                    [
                        6, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IUMUM"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MIUMUM", 
        "correct": "MIUMUMIUMUM", 
        "incorrect": "MIUMUIMUMUM", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 1.1136962009473257, 
        "stimulus": 333, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ], 
                    [
                        6, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IIIMI"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MIIIMI", 
        "correct": "MIIIMIIIIMI", 
        "incorrect": "MIIIIMIIIMI", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "<Mx>=<Mxx>", 
        "score": 0.6011541762738962, 
        "stimulus": 298, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UU"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UUI", 
        "correct": "UUIU", 
        "incorrect": "UIUU", 
        "length": 4, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 0.9035079029052512, 
        "stimulus": 368, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "II", 
        "correct": "IIU", 
        "incorrect": "IUI", 
        "length": 3, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 0.6535898384862245, 
        "stimulus": 370, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UIMUIIM"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UIMUIIMI", 
        "correct": "UIMUIIMIU", 
        "incorrect": "UIMUIIMUI", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 1.2185958257332383, 
        "stimulus": 919, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MMMI"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MMMII", 
        "correct": "MMMIIU", 
        "incorrect": "MMMIUI", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 1.1098404068981929, 
        "stimulus": 1176, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "I", 
        "correct": "IU", 
        "incorrect": "UI", 
        "length": 2, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 0.9428090415820634, 
        "stimulus": 358, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UUUIU"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UUUIUI", 
        "correct": "UUUIUIU", 
        "incorrect": "UUUIUUI", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 0.9749762204267015, 
        "stimulus": 512, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MUUIMIM"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MUUIMIMI", 
        "correct": "MUUIMIMIU", 
        "incorrect": "MUUIMIMUI", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 1.1915136990654975, 
        "stimulus": 957, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MU"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MUI", 
        "correct": "MUIU", 
        "incorrect": "MUUI", 
        "length": 4, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 1.101373060308832, 
        "stimulus": 371, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UUI"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UUII", 
        "correct": "UUIIU", 
        "incorrect": "UUIUI", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 0.8929879895249546, 
        "stimulus": 453, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        9, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        9, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        10, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IMUMUMMMM"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IMUMUMMMMI", 
        "correct": "IMUMUMMMMIU", 
        "incorrect": "IMUMUMMMMUI", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 1.4480799388500802, 
        "stimulus": 758, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        9, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MIIIIUII"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MIIIIUIII", 
        "correct": "MIIIIUIIIU", 
        "incorrect": "MIIIIUIIUI", 
        "length": 10, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 1.2453134823580823, 
        "stimulus": 967, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IM"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IMI", 
        "correct": "IMIU", 
        "incorrect": "IMUI", 
        "length": 4, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 0.8984041307564036, 
        "stimulus": 364, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MIIUU"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MIIUUI", 
        "correct": "MIIUUIU", 
        "incorrect": "MIIUUUI", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 1.0492473081879448, 
        "stimulus": 710, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UIIU"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UIIUI", 
        "correct": "UIIUIU", 
        "incorrect": "UIIUUI", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 0.9148349335649829, 
        "stimulus": 510, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UUMI"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UUMII", 
        "correct": "UUMIIU", 
        "incorrect": "UUMIUI", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 1.4021166948194028, 
        "stimulus": 526, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UM"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UMI", 
        "correct": "UMIU", 
        "incorrect": "UMUI", 
        "length": 4, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 0.4522037801745582, 
        "stimulus": 379, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MI"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MII", 
        "correct": "MIIU", 
        "incorrect": "MIUI", 
        "length": 4, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 0.9591920992658123, 
        "stimulus": 376, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MIM"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MIMI", 
        "correct": "MIMIU", 
        "incorrect": "MIMUI", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 1.17020498628644, 
        "stimulus": 398, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        9, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IIMMIMUU"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IIMMIMUUI", 
        "correct": "IIMMIMUUIU", 
        "incorrect": "IIMMIMUUUI", 
        "length": 10, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 1.428501463399102, 
        "stimulus": 616, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UIUII"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UIUIII", 
        "correct": "UIUIIIU", 
        "incorrect": "UIUIIUI", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 1.065127032872423, 
        "stimulus": 509, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IMM"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IMMI", 
        "correct": "IMMIU", 
        "incorrect": "IMMUI", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 1.051468172656947, 
        "stimulus": 436, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UUU"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UUUI", 
        "correct": "UUUIU", 
        "incorrect": "UUIUU", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 0.9609589524188824, 
        "stimulus": 507, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IUIU"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IUIUI", 
        "correct": "IUIUIU", 
        "incorrect": "IUIUUI", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 0.8838572772508256, 
        "stimulus": 620, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UMI"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UMII", 
        "correct": "UMIIU", 
        "incorrect": "UMIUI", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 1.0727724552488942, 
        "stimulus": 671, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IIUIIU"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IIUIIUI", 
        "correct": "IIUIIUIU", 
        "incorrect": "IIUIIUUI", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 1.0740405034689564, 
        "stimulus": 1257, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UMUIII"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UMUIIII", 
        "correct": "UMUIIIIU", 
        "incorrect": "UMUIIIUI", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 1.2261259809245006, 
        "stimulus": 674, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        9, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IIUUIIUI"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IIUUIIUII", 
        "correct": "IIUUIIUIIU", 
        "incorrect": "IIUUIIUIUI", 
        "length": 10, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 1.2027415310563574, 
        "stimulus": 1329, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IUM"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IUMI", 
        "correct": "IUMIU", 
        "incorrect": "IUMUI", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 1.065048168892448, 
        "stimulus": 547, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UUIIUMM"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UUIIUMMI", 
        "correct": "UUIIUMMIU", 
        "incorrect": "UUIIUMMUI", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 1.1203698521146288, 
        "stimulus": 982, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IUMU"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IUMUI", 
        "correct": "IUMUIU", 
        "incorrect": "IUMUUI", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 1.2837950760908612, 
        "stimulus": 581, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IMUMIUU"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IMUMIUUI", 
        "correct": "IMUMIUUIU", 
        "incorrect": "IMUMIUUUI", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 1.4869500872533075, 
        "stimulus": 474, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        9, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        9, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        10, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MUIMMMIMM"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MUIMMMIMMI", 
        "correct": "MUIMMMIMMIU", 
        "incorrect": "MUIMMMIMMUI", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 1.341937805411348, 
        "stimulus": 1279, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UI", 
        "correct": "UIU", 
        "incorrect": "UUI", 
        "length": 3, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 0.984723147373133, 
        "stimulus": 366, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UIIMM"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UIIMMI", 
        "correct": "UIIMMIU", 
        "incorrect": "UIIMMUI", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 1.34814863027565, 
        "stimulus": 1116, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UIMII"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UIMIII", 
        "correct": "UIMIIIU", 
        "incorrect": "UIMIIUI", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 0.552401913003699, 
        "stimulus": 692, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MI", 
        "correct": "MIU", 
        "incorrect": "MUI", 
        "length": 3, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 0.984723147373133, 
        "stimulus": 372, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "II"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "III", 
        "correct": "IIIU", 
        "incorrect": "IIUI", 
        "length": 4, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 0.9106698677405053, 
        "stimulus": 378, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UUUU"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UUUUI", 
        "correct": "UUUUIU", 
        "incorrect": "UUUIUU", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 0.8635550146673537, 
        "stimulus": 1226, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UMMMI"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UMMMII", 
        "correct": "UMMMIIU", 
        "incorrect": "UMMMIUI", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 1.247453553414845, 
        "stimulus": 518, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        9, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        9, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        10, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UIMUUIIUU"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UIMUUIIUUI", 
        "correct": "UIMUUIIUUIU", 
        "incorrect": "UIMUUIIUUUI", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 1.1885953787390147, 
        "stimulus": 1269, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UUM"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UUMI", 
        "correct": "UUMIU", 
        "incorrect": "UUMUI", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 0.8350886015456844, 
        "stimulus": 411, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IMMM"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IMMMI", 
        "correct": "IMMMIU", 
        "incorrect": "IMMMUI", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 1.211896392517936, 
        "stimulus": 880, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UUUMMU"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UUUMMUI", 
        "correct": "UUUMMUIU", 
        "incorrect": "UUUMMUUI", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 0.723103816278927, 
        "stimulus": 779, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UI"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UII", 
        "correct": "UIIU", 
        "incorrect": "UIUI", 
        "length": 4, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 0.9981756028243807, 
        "stimulus": 363, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IIMUI"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IIMUII", 
        "correct": "IIMUIIU", 
        "incorrect": "IIMUIUI", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 1.031283170644762, 
        "stimulus": 564, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MUMI"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MUMII", 
        "correct": "MUMIIU", 
        "incorrect": "MUMIUI", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 1.117262511765353, 
        "stimulus": 668, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UMIM"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UMIMI", 
        "correct": "UMIMIU", 
        "incorrect": "UMIMUI", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 1.2237192493158084, 
        "stimulus": 541, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UIMUUU"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UIMUUUI", 
        "correct": "UIMUUUIU", 
        "incorrect": "UIMUUIUU", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 1.0306891170432235, 
        "stimulus": 1048, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MUUMM"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MUUMMI", 
        "correct": "MUUMMIU", 
        "incorrect": "MUUMMUI", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 1.1709420351808146, 
        "stimulus": 1074, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UMMMIMM"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UMMMIMMI", 
        "correct": "UMMMIMMIU", 
        "incorrect": "UMMMIMMUI", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 1.3716974013441496, 
        "stimulus": 898, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        9, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        9, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        10, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UMUIMIMMI"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UMUIMIMMII", 
        "correct": "UMUIMIMMIIU", 
        "incorrect": "UMUIMIMMIUI", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 1.5125796329971544, 
        "stimulus": 890, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UMMIIM"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UMMIIMI", 
        "correct": "UMMIIMIU", 
        "incorrect": "UMMIIMUI", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 1.4367527660425452, 
        "stimulus": 575, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UIUU"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UIUUI", 
        "correct": "UIUUIU", 
        "incorrect": "UIUUUI", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 0.9625801653086287, 
        "stimulus": 1208, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MIMIMUU"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MIMIMUUI", 
        "correct": "MIMIMUUIU", 
        "incorrect": "MIMIMUUUI", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 1.3264126930944746, 
        "stimulus": 1335, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MUIUMI"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MUIUMII", 
        "correct": "MUIUMIIU", 
        "incorrect": "MUIUMIUI", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 1.2708331534185344, 
        "stimulus": 864, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UMMU"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UMMUI", 
        "correct": "UMMUIU", 
        "incorrect": "UMMUUI", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 1.2837950760908612, 
        "stimulus": 597, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        9, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IIMMIUMU"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IIMMIUMUI", 
        "correct": "IIMMIUMUIU", 
        "incorrect": "IIMMIUMUUI", 
        "length": 10, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 1.3181879875951563, 
        "stimulus": 971, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        9, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        9, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        10, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UMIIIMMUU"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UMIIIMMUUI", 
        "correct": "UMIIIMMUUIU", 
        "incorrect": "UMIIIMMUUUI", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 1.5051994045928319, 
        "stimulus": 811, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MIMII"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MIMIII", 
        "correct": "MIMIIIU", 
        "incorrect": "MIMIIUI", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 1.1254334218923967, 
        "stimulus": 1219, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MUMUMU"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MUMUMUI", 
        "correct": "MUMUMUIU", 
        "incorrect": "MUMUMUUI", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 1.0975251658170855, 
        "stimulus": 1173, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        9, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IMUIUIUU"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IMUIUIUUI", 
        "correct": "IMUIUIUUIU", 
        "incorrect": "IMUIUIUUUI", 
        "length": 10, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 1.4227742867906743, 
        "stimulus": 862, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IMII"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IMIII", 
        "correct": "IMIIIU", 
        "incorrect": "IMIIUI", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 0.9439435155927098, 
        "stimulus": 472, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IIMUIU"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IIMUIUI", 
        "correct": "IIMUIUIU", 
        "incorrect": "IIMUIUUI", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 1.405075108699957, 
        "stimulus": 1121, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MUM"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MUMI", 
        "correct": "MUMIU", 
        "incorrect": "MUMUI", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 0.9101248354599519, 
        "stimulus": 466, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IIU"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IIUI", 
        "correct": "IIUIU", 
        "incorrect": "IIUUI", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 0.5751951978601728, 
        "stimulus": 567, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MUMUMI"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MUMUMII", 
        "correct": "MUMUMIIU", 
        "incorrect": "MUMUMIUI", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 1.3563877067382188, 
        "stimulus": 1240, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MMU"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MMUI", 
        "correct": "MMUIU", 
        "incorrect": "MMUUI", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 0.894195130925229, 
        "stimulus": 393, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MUU"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MUUI", 
        "correct": "MUUIU", 
        "incorrect": "MUIUU", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 0.9609589524188824, 
        "stimulus": 689, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IMU"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IMUI", 
        "correct": "IMUIU", 
        "incorrect": "IMUUI", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 1.051468172656947, 
        "stimulus": 637, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        9, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UUUMIIII"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UUUMIIIII", 
        "correct": "UUUMIIIIIU", 
        "incorrect": "UUUMIIIIUI", 
        "length": 10, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 1.4124936333906983, 
        "stimulus": 882, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IUMI"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IUMII", 
        "correct": "IUMIIU", 
        "incorrect": "IUMIUI", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 1.1782420406622542, 
        "stimulus": 480, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MIIU"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MIIUI", 
        "correct": "MIIUIU", 
        "incorrect": "MIIUUI", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 0.9471633575499299, 
        "stimulus": 702, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        9, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        9, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        10, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IIMMIMIMI"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IIMMIMIMII", 
        "correct": "IIMMIMIMIIU", 
        "incorrect": "IIMMIMIMIUI", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 1.4643894942050162, 
        "stimulus": 524, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UMUIIUI"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UMUIIUII", 
        "correct": "UMUIIUIIU", 
        "incorrect": "UMUIIUIUI", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 1.3806037486483034, 
        "stimulus": 1308, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IUUUI"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IUUUII", 
        "correct": "IUUUIIU", 
        "incorrect": "IUUUIUI", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 0.7139045509097649, 
        "stimulus": 1098, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IIIM"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IIIMI", 
        "correct": "IIIMIU", 
        "incorrect": "IIIMUI", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 0.9515839536933032, 
        "stimulus": 525, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "III"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IIII", 
        "correct": "IIIIU", 
        "incorrect": "IIIUI", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 0.7411195299118166, 
        "stimulus": 478, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UMM"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UMMI", 
        "correct": "UMMIU", 
        "incorrect": "UMMUI", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 0.9026327115375886, 
        "stimulus": 585, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UMIUMUM"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UMIUMUMI", 
        "correct": "UMIUMUMIU", 
        "incorrect": "UMIUMUMUI", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 1.3740020111519275, 
        "stimulus": 1052, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MII"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MIII", 
        "correct": "MIIIU", 
        "incorrect": "MIIUI", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 1.051468172656947, 
        "stimulus": 468, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IMMI"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IMMII", 
        "correct": "IMMIIU", 
        "incorrect": "IMMIUI", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 0.8337599270580837, 
        "stimulus": 479, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IUIIU"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IUIIUI", 
        "correct": "IUIIUIU", 
        "incorrect": "IUIIUUI", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 1.1596229504077733, 
        "stimulus": 574, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        9, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        9, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        10, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UMIMIUMMI"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UMIMIUMMII", 
        "correct": "UMIMIUMMIIU", 
        "incorrect": "UMIMIUMMIUI", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 1.572852052337303, 
        "stimulus": 1185, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        9, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IIMIUMMU"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IIMIUMMUI", 
        "correct": "IIMIUMMUIU", 
        "incorrect": "IIMIUMMUUI", 
        "length": 10, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 1.2691568762539598, 
        "stimulus": 1107, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IU"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IUI", 
        "correct": "IUIU", 
        "incorrect": "IUUI", 
        "length": 4, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 1.0661695771284148, 
        "stimulus": 369, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        9, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        9, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        10, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IIMIUUMII"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IIMIUUMIII", 
        "correct": "IIMIUUMIIIU", 
        "incorrect": "IIMIUUMIIUI", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 1.3257743833069566, 
        "stimulus": 966, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        9, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IUMUUIUM"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IUMUUIUMI", 
        "correct": "IUMUUIUMIU", 
        "incorrect": "IUMUUIUMUI", 
        "length": 10, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 1.031434930628994, 
        "stimulus": 827, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UUIMUUU"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UUIMUUUI", 
        "correct": "UUIMUUUIU", 
        "incorrect": "UUIMUUIUU", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 1.1915136990654975, 
        "stimulus": 1311, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        9, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        9, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        10, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IIIIIUUUU"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IIIIIUUUUI", 
        "correct": "IIIIIUUUUIU", 
        "incorrect": "IIIIIUUUIUU", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 1.396500974814286, 
        "stimulus": 1099, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MIUMM"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MIUMMI", 
        "correct": "MIUMMIU", 
        "incorrect": "MIUMMUI", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 1.3887564917191784, 
        "stimulus": 377, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IMIIUIM"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IMIIUIMI", 
        "correct": "IMIIUIMIU", 
        "incorrect": "IMIIUIMUI", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 1.3580926354207743, 
        "stimulus": 1316, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IIII"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IIIII", 
        "correct": "IIIIIU", 
        "incorrect": "IIIIUI", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 0.9471633575499299, 
        "stimulus": 765, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MM"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MMI", 
        "correct": "MMIU", 
        "incorrect": "MMUI", 
        "length": 4, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 1.1703517839718756, 
        "stimulus": 399, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MUIUMMU"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MUIUMMUI", 
        "correct": "MUIUMMUIU", 
        "incorrect": "MUIUMMUUI", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 1.3365946985710304, 
        "stimulus": 1033, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MMM"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MMMI", 
        "correct": "MMMIU", 
        "incorrect": "MMMUI", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 0.6808891315541495, 
        "stimulus": 635, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        9, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IUMUMIUU"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IUMUMIUUI", 
        "correct": "IUMUMIUUIU", 
        "incorrect": "IUMUMIUUUI", 
        "length": 10, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 1.305550915128822, 
        "stimulus": 1011, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MMUI"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MMUII", 
        "correct": "MMUIIU", 
        "incorrect": "MMUIUI", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 1.2837950760908612, 
        "stimulus": 488, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IIMMUM"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IIMMUMI", 
        "correct": "IIMMUMIU", 
        "incorrect": "IIMMUMUI", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 1.3728065687142879, 
        "stimulus": 1080, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        9, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        9, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        10, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IMUUUIMUU"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IMUUUIMUUI", 
        "correct": "IMUUUIMUUIU", 
        "incorrect": "IMUUUIMUUUI", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 1.34596306830359, 
        "stimulus": 1113, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MUUIII"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MUUIIII", 
        "correct": "MUUIIIIU", 
        "incorrect": "MUUIIIUI", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 1.0748527941808517, 
        "stimulus": 1350, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UIMU"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UIMUI", 
        "correct": "UIMUIU", 
        "incorrect": "UIMUUI", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 1.0850630391754728, 
        "stimulus": 469, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IMUUUUI"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IMUUUUII", 
        "correct": "IMUUUUIIU", 
        "incorrect": "IMUUUUIUI", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 1.2284540298306192, 
        "stimulus": 760, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IMMIMI"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IMMIMII", 
        "correct": "IMMIMIIU", 
        "incorrect": "IMMIMIUI", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 1.231219644388291, 
        "stimulus": 1019, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        9, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MMMUMMIU"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MMMUMMIUI", 
        "correct": "MMMUMMIUIU", 
        "incorrect": "MMMUMMIUUI", 
        "length": 10, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 1.1458677174315859, 
        "stimulus": 773, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UIMUUII"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UIMUUIII", 
        "correct": "UIMUUIIIU", 
        "incorrect": "UIMUUIIUI", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 1.332062405367818, 
        "stimulus": 1030, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UII"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UIII", 
        "correct": "UIIIU", 
        "incorrect": "UIIUI", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 1.027717179997083, 
        "stimulus": 614, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UIIIMMM"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UIIIMMMI", 
        "correct": "UIIIMMMIU", 
        "incorrect": "UIIIMMMUI", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 1.3137552453323746, 
        "stimulus": 956, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        9, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        9, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        10, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MIUIUIUUI"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MIUIUIUUII", 
        "correct": "MIUIUIUUIIU", 
        "incorrect": "MIUIUIUUIUI", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 1.533966412189916, 
        "stimulus": 875, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UIMMM"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UIMMMI", 
        "correct": "UIMMMIU", 
        "incorrect": "UIMMMUI", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 1.1593116427353982, 
        "stimulus": 946, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        9, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IIUMMMIM"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IIUMMMIMI", 
        "correct": "IIUMMMIMIU", 
        "incorrect": "IIUMMMIMUI", 
        "length": 10, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 1.3036186218922765, 
        "stimulus": 1238, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IIMUII"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IIMUIII", 
        "correct": "IIMUIIIU", 
        "incorrect": "IIMUIIUI", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 1.0769494212781487, 
        "stimulus": 387, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UIU"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UIUI", 
        "correct": "UIUIU", 
        "incorrect": "UIUUI", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 0.6333061472425722, 
        "stimulus": 538, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IMUUIM"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IMUUIMI", 
        "correct": "IMUUIMIU", 
        "incorrect": "IMUUIMUI", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 1.4057500708709838, 
        "stimulus": 1270, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MIIM"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MIIMI", 
        "correct": "MIIMIU", 
        "incorrect": "MIIMUI", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 1.1893638893287914, 
        "stimulus": 654, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        9, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UUMIUUUI"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UUMIUUUII", 
        "correct": "UUMIUUUIIU", 
        "incorrect": "UUMIUUUIUI", 
        "length": 10, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 1.2008192114044185, 
        "stimulus": 679, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IMMU"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IMMUI", 
        "correct": "IMMUIU", 
        "incorrect": "IMMUUI", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 0.40655781409087083, 
        "stimulus": 421, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IUU"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IUUI", 
        "correct": "IUUIU", 
        "incorrect": "IUIUU", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 0.760107292353071, 
        "stimulus": 383, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IUUI"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IUUII", 
        "correct": "IUUIIU", 
        "incorrect": "IUUIUI", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 1.183798880520513, 
        "stimulus": 484, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UUMII"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UUMIII", 
        "correct": "UUMIIIU", 
        "incorrect": "UUMIIUI", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 1.3482154463271379, 
        "stimulus": 854, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UMMUIII"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UMMUIIII", 
        "correct": "UMMUIIIIU", 
        "incorrect": "UMMUIIIUI", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 1.4983300730389097, 
        "stimulus": 1296, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UMUMIIU"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UMUMIIUI", 
        "correct": "UMUMIIUIU", 
        "incorrect": "UMUMIIUUI", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 1.2931483252186056, 
        "stimulus": 848, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        9, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        9, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        10, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IUIIMIUUI"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IUIIMIUUII", 
        "correct": "IUIIMIUUIIU", 
        "incorrect": "IUIIMIUUIUI", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 1.0008946134450503, 
        "stimulus": 1071, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UMUM"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UMUMI", 
        "correct": "UMUMIU", 
        "incorrect": "UMUMUI", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 0.9642127904773886, 
        "stimulus": 489, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MIMMMUU"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MIMMMUUI", 
        "correct": "MIMMMUUIU", 
        "incorrect": "MIMMMUUUI", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 1.1435859948079439, 
        "stimulus": 1145, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        9, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        9, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        10, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IIMUIUMUM"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IIMUIUMUMI", 
        "correct": "IIMUIUMUMIU", 
        "incorrect": "IIMUIUMUMUI", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 1.540377517980919, 
        "stimulus": 888, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IIMUUU"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IIMUUUI", 
        "correct": "IIMUUUIU", 
        "incorrect": "IIMUUIUU", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 1.3793299526520784, 
        "stimulus": 715, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UUIIM"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UUIIMI", 
        "correct": "UUIIMIU", 
        "incorrect": "UUIIMUI", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 1.3165351360930884, 
        "stimulus": 1022, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IMIUUU"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IMIUUUI", 
        "correct": "IMIUUUIU", 
        "incorrect": "IMIUUIUU", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 1.407364955611438, 
        "stimulus": 1128, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IIUIU"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IIUIUI", 
        "correct": "IIUIUIU", 
        "incorrect": "IIUIUUI", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 0.9091533215816752, 
        "stimulus": 536, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        9, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        9, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        10, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MUUUIIMMM"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MUUUIIMMMI", 
        "correct": "MUUUIIMMMIU", 
        "incorrect": "MUUUIIMMMUI", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 1.536114533238513, 
        "stimulus": 1177, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        9, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UUUIMIMI"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UUUIMIMII", 
        "correct": "UUUIMIMIIU", 
        "incorrect": "UUUIMIMIUI", 
        "length": 10, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 1.561464872324313, 
        "stimulus": 1205, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MIIMMM"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MIIMMMI", 
        "correct": "MIIMMMIU", 
        "incorrect": "MIIMMMUI", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 1.2951711616865997, 
        "stimulus": 844, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        9, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IUMUIMMU"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IUMUIMMUI", 
        "correct": "IUMUIMMUIU", 
        "incorrect": "IUMUIMMUUI", 
        "length": 10, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 1.3600803168955404, 
        "stimulus": 1283, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UUMU"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UUMUI", 
        "correct": "UUMUIU", 
        "incorrect": "UUMUUI", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 1.2546138903506316, 
        "stimulus": 390, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IMUMUI"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IMUMUII", 
        "correct": "IMUMUIIU", 
        "incorrect": "IMUMUIUI", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 1.3506411916163041, 
        "stimulus": 1206, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        9, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        9, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        10, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MUMIIUUUM"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MUMIIUUUMI", 
        "correct": "MUMIIUUUMIU", 
        "incorrect": "MUMIIUUUMUI", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 1.2915320407914286, 
        "stimulus": 1209, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IUMMUM"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IUMMUMI", 
        "correct": "IUMMUMIU", 
        "incorrect": "IUMMUMUI", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 1.343438531202598, 
        "stimulus": 1151, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MIMU"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MIMUI", 
        "correct": "MIMUIU", 
        "incorrect": "MIMUUI", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 1.1939740675220856, 
        "stimulus": 566, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UIIMUM"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UIIMUMI", 
        "correct": "UIIMUMIU", 
        "incorrect": "UIIMUMUI", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 1.44988699121512, 
        "stimulus": 1290, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MIUII"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MIUIII", 
        "correct": "MIUIIIU", 
        "incorrect": "MIUIIUI", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 1.2601928170954748, 
        "stimulus": 1129, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UMU"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UMUI", 
        "correct": "UMUIU", 
        "incorrect": "UMUUI", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 1.3295342009181745, 
        "stimulus": 392, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        9, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IMMIMUUI"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IMMIMUUII", 
        "correct": "IMMIMUUIIU", 
        "incorrect": "IMMIMUUIUI", 
        "length": 10, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 1.3723228342885736, 
        "stimulus": 1352, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IIUU"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IIUUI", 
        "correct": "IIUUIU", 
        "incorrect": "IIUUUI", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 0.9439435155927098, 
        "stimulus": 835, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IMMIUUI"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IMMIUUII", 
        "correct": "IMMIUUIIU", 
        "incorrect": "IMMIUUIUI", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 1.3456005705683816, 
        "stimulus": 1082, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IUI"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IUII", 
        "correct": "IUIIU", 
        "incorrect": "IUIUI", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 0.3467006886252971, 
        "stimulus": 444, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UIIIUM"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UIIIUMI", 
        "correct": "UIIIUMIU", 
        "incorrect": "UIIIUMUI", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 1.3939619039025255, 
        "stimulus": 408, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UUIU"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UUIUI", 
        "correct": "UUIUIU", 
        "incorrect": "UUIUUI", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 0.559563715162477, 
        "stimulus": 582, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UIIMUUM"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UIIMUUMI", 
        "correct": "UIIMUUMIU", 
        "incorrect": "UIIMUUMUI", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 1.3856072824691616, 
        "stimulus": 1255, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MUUMIM"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MUUMIMI", 
        "correct": "MUUMIMIU", 
        "incorrect": "MUUMIMUI", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 1.2867676715228649, 
        "stimulus": 1213, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MIMI"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MIMII", 
        "correct": "MIMIIU", 
        "incorrect": "MIMIUI", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 0.9439938420569388, 
        "stimulus": 410, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        9, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        9, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        10, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IUUIIIMUM"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IUUIIIMUMI", 
        "correct": "IUUIIIMUMIU", 
        "incorrect": "IUUIIIMUMUI", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 1.3155574606661675, 
        "stimulus": 781, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MUMUM"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MUMUMI", 
        "correct": "MUMUMIU", 
        "incorrect": "MUMUMUI", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 1.240078648686106, 
        "stimulus": 1216, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        9, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UMMIUMUI"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UMMIUMUII", 
        "correct": "UMMIUMUIIU", 
        "incorrect": "UMMIUMUIUI", 
        "length": 10, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 1.3036582077332066, 
        "stimulus": 1233, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IMIU"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IMIUI", 
        "correct": "IMIUIU", 
        "incorrect": "IMIUUI", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 1.192210949642544, 
        "stimulus": 374, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MMUMUI"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MMUMUII", 
        "correct": "MMUMUIIU", 
        "incorrect": "MMUMUIUI", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 1.1266537633381166, 
        "stimulus": 528, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UUIUMI"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UUIUMII", 
        "correct": "UUIUMIIU", 
        "incorrect": "UUIUMIUI", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 1.2093927337508645, 
        "stimulus": 535, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UIII"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UIIII", 
        "correct": "UIIIIU", 
        "incorrect": "UIIIUI", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 1.1635459930681282, 
        "stimulus": 948, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IMIM"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IMIMI", 
        "correct": "IMIMIU", 
        "incorrect": "IMIMUI", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 0.8930145017643975, 
        "stimulus": 460, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IMIMIM"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IMIMIMI", 
        "correct": "IMIMIMIU", 
        "incorrect": "IMIMIMUI", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 0.9409827700662711, 
        "stimulus": 1285, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        9, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        9, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        10, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MMMMUIMMU"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MMMMUIMMUI", 
        "correct": "MMMMUIMMUIU", 
        "incorrect": "MMMMUIMMUUI", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 1.1599912744635164, 
        "stimulus": 1275, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IMUMM"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IMUMMI", 
        "correct": "IMUMMIU", 
        "incorrect": "IMUMMUI", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 1.3054279037290109, 
        "stimulus": 683, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        9, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MIIIUMMU"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MIIIUMMUI", 
        "correct": "MIIIUMMUIU", 
        "incorrect": "MIIIUMMUUI", 
        "length": 10, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 1.5305957792850529, 
        "stimulus": 483, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IIMMUI"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IIMMUII", 
        "correct": "IIMMUIIU", 
        "incorrect": "IIMMUIUI", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 1.2161457012396795, 
        "stimulus": 448, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IUMIMM"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IUMIMMI", 
        "correct": "IUMIMMIU", 
        "incorrect": "IUMIMMUI", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 1.2390504896259853, 
        "stimulus": 1008, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        9, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MUIIUIIM"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MUIIUIIMI", 
        "correct": "MUIIUIIMIU", 
        "incorrect": "MUIIUIIMUI", 
        "length": 10, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 1.439803113681132, 
        "stimulus": 914, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IMUIIM"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IMUIIMI", 
        "correct": "IMUIIMIU", 
        "incorrect": "IMUIIMUI", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 1.4017228995489064, 
        "stimulus": 961, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        9, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        9, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        10, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UUUIMMIUI"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UUUIMMIUII", 
        "correct": "UUUIMMIUIIU", 
        "incorrect": "UUUIMMIUIUI", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 1.5202566834668951, 
        "stimulus": 1280, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IIIUUI"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IIIUUII", 
        "correct": "IIIUUIIU", 
        "incorrect": "IIIUUIUI", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 0.6898331094087966, 
        "stimulus": 804, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        9, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UIUMMIII"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UIUMMIIII", 
        "correct": "UIUMMIIIIU", 
        "incorrect": "UIUMMIIIUI", 
        "length": 10, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 1.3763539856882008, 
        "stimulus": 784, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MMMUU"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MMMUUI", 
        "correct": "MMMUUIU", 
        "incorrect": "MMMUUUI", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 0.8999695042511935, 
        "stimulus": 595, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IMMMIU"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IMMMIUI", 
        "correct": "IMMMIUIU", 
        "incorrect": "IMMMIUUI", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 0.917032341689114, 
        "stimulus": 1276, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IUUU"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IUUUI", 
        "correct": "IUUUIU", 
        "incorrect": "IUUIUU", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 0.7496555682941201, 
        "stimulus": 462, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        9, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MIMIUIMI"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MIMIUIMII", 
        "correct": "MIMIUIMIIU", 
        "incorrect": "MIMIUIMIUI", 
        "length": 10, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 1.3429062983253919, 
        "stimulus": 977, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UUMMIMI"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UUMMIMII", 
        "correct": "UUMMIMIIU", 
        "incorrect": "UUMMIMIUI", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 1.3394160794194978, 
        "stimulus": 1299, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UIIIMMI"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UIIIMMII", 
        "correct": "UIIIMMIIU", 
        "incorrect": "UIIIMMIUI", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 1.358240289421389, 
        "stimulus": 1006, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IMMMMUM"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IMMMMUMI", 
        "correct": "IMMMMUMIU", 
        "incorrect": "IMMMMUMUI", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 1.039859640931255, 
        "stimulus": 1130, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UUIIUU"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UUIIUUI", 
        "correct": "UUIIUUIU", 
        "incorrect": "UUIIUUUI", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 0.8137066657024766, 
        "stimulus": 471, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        9, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        9, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        10, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IIMIUIMUM"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IIMIUIMUMI", 
        "correct": "IIMIUIMUMIU", 
        "incorrect": "IIMIUIMUMUI", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 1.3021759595172384, 
        "stimulus": 1268, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MMI"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MMII", 
        "correct": "MMIIU", 
        "incorrect": "MMIUI", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 1.3158793568145928, 
        "stimulus": 380, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MUIU"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MUIUI", 
        "correct": "MUIUIU", 
        "incorrect": "MUIUUI", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 1.2968572900250754, 
        "stimulus": 425, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        9, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MIUIMMMM"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MIUIMMMMI", 
        "correct": "MIUIMMMMIU", 
        "incorrect": "MIUIMMMMUI", 
        "length": 10, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 1.3690737916103903, 
        "stimulus": 790, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UIIUU"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UIIUUI", 
        "correct": "UIIUUIU", 
        "incorrect": "UIIUUUI", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 0.801801922363141, 
        "stimulus": 1326, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IIM"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IIMI", 
        "correct": "IIMIU", 
        "incorrect": "IIMUI", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 0.5751951978601728, 
        "stimulus": 583, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UMUIMI"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UMUIMII", 
        "correct": "UMUIMIIU", 
        "incorrect": "UMUIMIUI", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 1.4370184934936172, 
        "stimulus": 1351, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UUUMUM"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UUUMUMI", 
        "correct": "UUUMUMIU", 
        "incorrect": "UUUMUMUI", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 0.5452226436663656, 
        "stimulus": 1069, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        9, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MUIMMIIU"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MUIMMIIUI", 
        "correct": "MUIMMIIUIU", 
        "incorrect": "MUIMMIIUUI", 
        "length": 10, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 1.4746784244741051, 
        "stimulus": 617, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UUMMUUU"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UUMMUUUI", 
        "correct": "UUMMUUUIU", 
        "incorrect": "UUMMUUIUU", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 1.2978628692799294, 
        "stimulus": 915, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        9, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        9, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        10, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MUUUUIIMM"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MUUUUIIMMI", 
        "correct": "MUUUUIIMMIU", 
        "incorrect": "MUUUUIIMMUI", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 1.4666149552050904, 
        "stimulus": 1200, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MMIMIUU"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MMIMIUUI", 
        "correct": "MMIMIUUIU", 
        "incorrect": "MMIMIUUUI", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 1.3559919561622635, 
        "stimulus": 562, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IUMMUU"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IUMMUUI", 
        "correct": "IUMMUUIU", 
        "incorrect": "IUMMUUUI", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 1.2437122244825443, 
        "stimulus": 454, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        9, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UUIUUUMI"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UUIUUUMII", 
        "correct": "UUIUUUMIIU", 
        "incorrect": "UUIUUUMIUI", 
        "length": 10, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 1.162271153875743, 
        "stimulus": 486, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IIMU"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IIMUI", 
        "correct": "IIMUIU", 
        "incorrect": "IIMUUI", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 1.2186955693532693, 
        "stimulus": 523, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IUUUUIM"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IUUUUIMI", 
        "correct": "IUUUUIMIU", 
        "incorrect": "IUUUUIMUI", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 1.5167500459660808, 
        "stimulus": 866, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MUIM"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MUIMI", 
        "correct": "MUIMIU", 
        "incorrect": "MUIMUI", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 1.0613609847758942, 
        "stimulus": 814, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IIUI"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IIUII", 
        "correct": "IIUIIU", 
        "incorrect": "IIUIUI", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 1.164608363683384, 
        "stimulus": 572, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MMMUMUM"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MMMUMUMI", 
        "correct": "MMMUMUMIU", 
        "incorrect": "MMMUMUMUI", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 1.268921281152139, 
        "stimulus": 1063, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        9, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        9, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        10, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IIUIUMIMM"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IIUIUMIMMI", 
        "correct": "IIUIUMIMMIU", 
        "incorrect": "IIUIUMIMMUI", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 1.5900582842302196, 
        "stimulus": 1324, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        9, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UMIIIMUI"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UMIIIMUII", 
        "correct": "UMIIIMUIIU", 
        "incorrect": "UMIIIMUIUI", 
        "length": 10, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 0.6679569883472128, 
        "stimulus": 516, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MMIII"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MMIIII", 
        "correct": "MMIIIIU", 
        "incorrect": "MMIIIUI", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 1.0900401657887768, 
        "stimulus": 1264, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MIMIMMM"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MIMIMMMI", 
        "correct": "MIMIMMMIU", 
        "incorrect": "MIMIMMMUI", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 1.103633524550809, 
        "stimulus": 936, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        9, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MUMIUMUI"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MUMIUMUII", 
        "correct": "MUMIUMUIIU", 
        "incorrect": "MUMIUMUIUI", 
        "length": 10, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 1.3182316952870354, 
        "stimulus": 905, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MUI"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MUII", 
        "correct": "MUIIU", 
        "incorrect": "MUIUI", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 1.0772301630957883, 
        "stimulus": 465, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        9, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        9, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        10, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IMIUUUIUU"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IMIUUUIUUI", 
        "correct": "IMIUUUIUUIU", 
        "incorrect": "IMIUUUIUUUI", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 1.274108088744767, 
        "stimulus": 423, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UIMMIMI"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UIMMIMII", 
        "correct": "UIMMIMIIU", 
        "incorrect": "UIMMIMIUI", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 1.227539447769705, 
        "stimulus": 638, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        9, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        9, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        10, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UIIUUMIMU"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UIIUUMIMUI", 
        "correct": "UIIUUMIMUIU", 
        "incorrect": "UIIUUMIMUUI", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 1.5120405496888167, 
        "stimulus": 1119, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        9, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        9, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        10, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UUIIUUMII"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UUIIUUMIII", 
        "correct": "UUIIUUMIIIU", 
        "incorrect": "UUIIUUMIIUI", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 1.4934831778801347, 
        "stimulus": 429, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MUUMUII"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MUUMUIII", 
        "correct": "MUUMUIIIU", 
        "incorrect": "MUUMUIIUI", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 1.3853074954048201, 
        "stimulus": 669, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UUMUUUM"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UUMUUUMI", 
        "correct": "UUMUUUMIU", 
        "incorrect": "UUMUUUMUI", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 1.0985020386881532, 
        "stimulus": 776, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MMUU"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MMUUI", 
        "correct": "MMUUIU", 
        "incorrect": "MMUUUI", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 1.1939740675220856, 
        "stimulus": 744, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UUIUUMI"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UUIUUMII", 
        "correct": "UUIUUMIIU", 
        "incorrect": "UUIUUMIUI", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 1.2964958934041937, 
        "stimulus": 445, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        9, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        9, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        10, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UIMUMIUMU"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UIMUMIUMUI", 
        "correct": "UIMUMIUMUIU", 
        "incorrect": "UIMUMIUMUUI", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 1.4151239078669453, 
        "stimulus": 655, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IMMIMU"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IMMIMUI", 
        "correct": "IMMIMUIU", 
        "incorrect": "IMMIMUUI", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 1.3352929847852062, 
        "stimulus": 818, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        9, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        9, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        10, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UMMIIMMUU"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UMMIIMMUUI", 
        "correct": "UMMIIMMUUIU", 
        "incorrect": "UMMIIMMUUUI", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 0.9562778883253447, 
        "stimulus": 684, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UUUMU"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UUUMUI", 
        "correct": "UUUMUIU", 
        "incorrect": "UUUMUUI", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 1.124213021864143, 
        "stimulus": 519, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MIMM"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MIMMI", 
        "correct": "MIMMIU", 
        "incorrect": "MIMMUI", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 1.0918634183202076, 
        "stimulus": 1061, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UUIMMIU"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UUIMMIUI", 
        "correct": "UUIMMIUIU", 
        "incorrect": "UUIMMIUUI", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 1.4777988947836824, 
        "stimulus": 929, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MIUI"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MIUII", 
        "correct": "MIUIIU", 
        "incorrect": "MIUIUI", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 1.155536276817946, 
        "stimulus": 675, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IUMUUUI"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IUMUUUII", 
        "correct": "IUMUUUIIU", 
        "incorrect": "IUMUUUIUI", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 1.3672814722654612, 
        "stimulus": 499, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IIMM"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IIMMI", 
        "correct": "IIMMIU", 
        "incorrect": "IIMMUI", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 1.183798880520513, 
        "stimulus": 619, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        9, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        9, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        10, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UMMIUMMII"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UMMIUMMIII", 
        "correct": "UMMIUMMIIIU", 
        "incorrect": "UMMIUMMIIUI", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 1.6407224718804871, 
        "stimulus": 837, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MIIIUI"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MIIIUII", 
        "correct": "MIIIUIIU", 
        "incorrect": "MIIIUIUI", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 0.9779379281594663, 
        "stimulus": 612, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IMIMMMM"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IMIMMMMI", 
        "correct": "IMIMMMMIU", 
        "incorrect": "IMIMMMMUI", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 1.150537332130296, 
        "stimulus": 514, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IUIIIUU"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IUIIIUUI", 
        "correct": "IUIIIUUIU", 
        "incorrect": "IUIIIUUUI", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 1.2019399821220569, 
        "stimulus": 832, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IMUIM"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IMUIMI", 
        "correct": "IMUIMIU", 
        "incorrect": "IMUIMUI", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 1.3217534553113612, 
        "stimulus": 1060, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        9, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IIIIUMMU"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IIIIUMMUI", 
        "correct": "IIIIUMMUIU", 
        "incorrect": "IIIIUMMUUI", 
        "length": 10, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 1.480541196704809, 
        "stimulus": 910, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UUUUI"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UUUUII", 
        "correct": "UUUUIIU", 
        "incorrect": "UUUUIUI", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 0.9106589665639344, 
        "stimulus": 550, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UIUMUM"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UIUMUMI", 
        "correct": "UIUMUMIU", 
        "incorrect": "UIUMUMUI", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 1.352861077498004, 
        "stimulus": 1272, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MUUI"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MUUII", 
        "correct": "MUUIIU", 
        "incorrect": "MUUIUI", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 1.336724387443837, 
        "stimulus": 382, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UMIMUIM"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UMIMUIMI", 
        "correct": "UMIMUIMIU", 
        "incorrect": "UMIMUIMUI", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 1.2771806454638113, 
        "stimulus": 1273, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UIIM"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UIIMI", 
        "correct": "UIIMIU", 
        "incorrect": "UIIMUI", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 1.0418500023321455, 
        "stimulus": 690, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IIUMMM"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IIUMMMI", 
        "correct": "IIUMMMIU", 
        "incorrect": "IIUMMMUI", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 1.4823123095314148, 
        "stimulus": 1334, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UIIIM"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UIIIMI", 
        "correct": "UIIIMIU", 
        "incorrect": "UIIIMUI", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 1.2379304216611162, 
        "stimulus": 817, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        9, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        9, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        10, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MMUUIIIUM"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MMUUIIIUMI", 
        "correct": "MMUUIIIUMIU", 
        "incorrect": "MMUUIIIUMUI", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 1.3086011158718438, 
        "stimulus": 604, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IIIUIUI"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IIIUIUII", 
        "correct": "IIIUIUIIU", 
        "incorrect": "IIIUIUIUI", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 0.9117118629606487, 
        "stimulus": 1305, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MIIIUU"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MIIIUUI", 
        "correct": "MIIIUUIU", 
        "incorrect": "MIIIUUUI", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 1.415250764355449, 
        "stimulus": 873, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MMUUII"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MMUUIII", 
        "correct": "MMUUIIIU", 
        "incorrect": "MMUUIIUI", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 1.372770692990533, 
        "stimulus": 816, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UUMUIUI"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UUMUIUII", 
        "correct": "UUMUIUIIU", 
        "incorrect": "UUMUIUIUI", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 1.2039409534965089, 
        "stimulus": 1042, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UMIMI"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UMIMII", 
        "correct": "UMIMIIU", 
        "incorrect": "UMIMIUI", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 1.2549865330411745, 
        "stimulus": 493, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MIUMI"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MIUMII", 
        "correct": "MIUMIIU", 
        "incorrect": "MIUMIUI", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 1.2489300721214434, 
        "stimulus": 517, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MUUMII"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MUUMIII", 
        "correct": "MUUMIIIU", 
        "incorrect": "MUUMIIUI", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 1.3653651984826731, 
        "stimulus": 825, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        9, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        9, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        10, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UUMMIMMII"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UUMMIMMIII", 
        "correct": "UUMMIMMIIIU", 
        "incorrect": "UUMMIMMIIUI", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 1.5712505219182737, 
        "stimulus": 799, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IMI"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IMII", 
        "correct": "IMIIU", 
        "incorrect": "IMIUI", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 0.8717260497225378, 
        "stimulus": 367, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        9, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        9, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        10, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MUMUMIUIM"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MUMUMIUIMI", 
        "correct": "MUMUMIUIMIU", 
        "incorrect": "MUMUMIUIMUI", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 1.3834512216044965, 
        "stimulus": 892, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        9, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IUIUMIII"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IUIUMIIII", 
        "correct": "IUIUMIIIIU", 
        "incorrect": "IUIUMIIIUI", 
        "length": 10, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 1.3123171974402486, 
        "stimulus": 970, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MMUUMUU"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MMUUMUUI", 
        "correct": "MMUUMUUIU", 
        "incorrect": "MMUUMUUUI", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 1.1323829414392528, 
        "stimulus": 1041, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        9, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UIMIUIIM"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UIMIUIIMI", 
        "correct": "UIMIUIIMIU", 
        "incorrect": "UIMIUIIMUI", 
        "length": 10, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 1.4082050103265915, 
        "stimulus": 791, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        9, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UUUUIIUI"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UUUUIIUII", 
        "correct": "UUUUIIUIIU", 
        "incorrect": "UUUUIIUIUI", 
        "length": 10, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 0.7972692151198224, 
        "stimulus": 540, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MIUU"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MIUUI", 
        "correct": "MIUUIU", 
        "incorrect": "MIUUUI", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 1.0613609847758942, 
        "stimulus": 412, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IUUIIUU"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IUUIIUUI", 
        "correct": "IUUIIUUIU", 
        "incorrect": "IUUIIUUUI", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 1.2150648797730117, 
        "stimulus": 1132, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UIUI"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UIUII", 
        "correct": "UIUIIU", 
        "incorrect": "UIUIUI", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 1.183798880520513, 
        "stimulus": 580, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IUIUMMU"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IUIUMMUI", 
        "correct": "IUIUMMUIU", 
        "incorrect": "IUIUMMUUI", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 1.1943005891780112, 
        "stimulus": 433, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MIIIU"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MIIIUI", 
        "correct": "MIIIUIU", 
        "incorrect": "MIIIUUI", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 0.9781600168736225, 
        "stimulus": 633, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IIMIM"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IIMIMI", 
        "correct": "IIMIMIU", 
        "incorrect": "IIMIMUI", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 1.0256249132582347, 
        "stimulus": 578, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MIMMMI"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MIMMMII", 
        "correct": "MIMMMIIU", 
        "incorrect": "MIMMMIUI", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 1.159669645641575, 
        "stimulus": 662, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        9, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        9, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        10, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MIUUMMMII"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MIUUMMMIII", 
        "correct": "MIUUMMMIIIU", 
        "incorrect": "MIUUMMMIIUI", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 1.3491360569633948, 
        "stimulus": 1250, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UMIIM"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UMIIMI", 
        "correct": "UMIIMIU", 
        "incorrect": "UMIIMUI", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "I>=IU>", 
        "score": 0.9220842708213922, 
        "stimulus": 360, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "III", 
        "correct": "U", 
        "incorrect": "I", 
        "length": 3, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 1.4987328137609317, 
        "stimulus": 1359, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MIII", 
        "correct": "MU", 
        "incorrect": "IU", 
        "length": 4, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 0.4461103471896025, 
        "stimulus": 1369, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MM"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MMIII", 
        "correct": "MMU", 
        "incorrect": "MIU", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 0.7858837088065351, 
        "stimulus": 1520, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        9, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IMMIIM"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IMMIIMIII", 
        "correct": "IMMIIMU", 
        "incorrect": "IMMIIMI", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 1.0519019878202942, 
        "stimulus": 2139, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UMU"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MIIIUMU", 
        "correct": "MUUMU", 
        "incorrect": "UMUMU", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 0.49376435729923235, 
        "stimulus": 1621, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IIU"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UUU"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UUUIIIIIU", 
        "correct": "UUUUIIU", 
        "incorrect": "UUIIUIU", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 0.5978900626561369, 
        "stimulus": 1465, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MMUU"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IIIMMUU", 
        "correct": "UMMUU", 
        "incorrect": "IUMUU", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 0.808431553586717, 
        "stimulus": 1908, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IIIM", 
        "correct": "UM", 
        "incorrect": "MU", 
        "length": 4, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 0.8153322575420074, 
        "stimulus": 1392, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UMIU"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UII"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UIIIIIUMIU", 
        "correct": "UIIUUMIU", 
        "incorrect": "UIIUIMIU", 
        "length": 10, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 0.810903259089417, 
        "stimulus": 1578, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MIIIM", 
        "correct": "MUM", 
        "incorrect": "MMU", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 0.6533110630247689, 
        "stimulus": 1464, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "II"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IIIII", 
        "correct": "IIU", 
        "incorrect": "III", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 1.0041850521978635, 
        "stimulus": 1381, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MIUUI"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UII"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UIIIIIMIUUI", 
        "correct": "UIIUMIUUI", 
        "incorrect": "UIIIUIUUI", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 0.7728025726897356, 
        "stimulus": 2046, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IUIM"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IIIIUIM", 
        "correct": "UIUIM", 
        "incorrect": "UUIIM", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 0.8410039499933393, 
        "stimulus": 2001, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IU"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UUIM"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UUIMIIIIU", 
        "correct": "UUIMUIU", 
        "incorrect": "UUIUIIU", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 0.7277438003448611, 
        "stimulus": 1427, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UI"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MIIIUI", 
        "correct": "MUUI", 
        "incorrect": "UMUI", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 0.4158410222996393, 
        "stimulus": 1556, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IMUIU"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IMUIUIII", 
        "correct": "IMUIUU", 
        "incorrect": "IMUIUI", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 1.1299207360277084, 
        "stimulus": 2254, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UUII"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IIIUUII", 
        "correct": "UUUII", 
        "incorrect": "UIUII", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 0.7364529812296715, 
        "stimulus": 1865, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "II"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MIMM"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MIMMIIIII", 
        "correct": "MIMMUII", 
        "incorrect": "MIMUIII", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 0.771165949035317, 
        "stimulus": 2176, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IMM"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IMMIIIM", 
        "correct": "IMMUM", 
        "incorrect": "IMMMU", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 0.6738425941825277, 
        "stimulus": 1618, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UUU"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IM"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IMIIIUUU", 
        "correct": "IMUUUU", 
        "incorrect": "IUIUUU", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 0.6425639521150106, 
        "stimulus": 1861, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        9, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UU"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MMMIMI"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MMMIMIIIIUU", 
        "correct": "MMMIMIUUU", 
        "incorrect": "MMMIMIUIU", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 1.0079679140810216, 
        "stimulus": 2092, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UIII", 
        "correct": "UU", 
        "incorrect": "IU", 
        "length": 4, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 0.9190718227089205, 
        "stimulus": 1364, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MUU"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MUUIIIM", 
        "correct": "MUUUM", 
        "incorrect": "MUUMU", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 0.8267566123697121, 
        "stimulus": 1577, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "III"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IIIIII", 
        "correct": "UIII", 
        "incorrect": "IIII", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 1.0506462776294154, 
        "stimulus": 1568, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IIIU", 
        "correct": "UU", 
        "incorrect": "UI", 
        "length": 4, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 1.2673337052748759, 
        "stimulus": 1361, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IIUI"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IIUIIIIM", 
        "correct": "IIUIUM", 
        "incorrect": "IIUIMU", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 0.5732092079404555, 
        "stimulus": 2051, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MIM"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MIMIIII", 
        "correct": "MIMUI", 
        "incorrect": "MIIUI", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 0.7952648552033698, 
        "stimulus": 2301, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IU"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IUIII", 
        "correct": "IUU", 
        "incorrect": "UIU", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 0.6715245360630289, 
        "stimulus": 1472, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MMII"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MMIIIII", 
        "correct": "MMIIU", 
        "incorrect": "MIIIU", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 0.9493940760299094, 
        "stimulus": 2025, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UIUM"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UIIIUIUM", 
        "correct": "UUUIUM", 
        "incorrect": "UUIUUM", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 0.763831239245891, 
        "stimulus": 2123, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MI"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IU"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IUIIIMI", 
        "correct": "IUUMI", 
        "incorrect": "IUMUI", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 0.5634978284025234, 
        "stimulus": 1446, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IMII"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UMM"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UMMIIIIMII", 
        "correct": "UMMUIMII", 
        "incorrect": "UMUIIMII", 
        "length": 10, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 0.7788993659122044, 
        "stimulus": 2219, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "II"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IIIIIM", 
        "correct": "IIUM", 
        "incorrect": "IIMU", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 0.6973841254328983, 
        "stimulus": 1390, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UUIII"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IIIIUUIII", 
        "correct": "IUUUIII", 
        "incorrect": "UIIUIII", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 0.46174104099633706, 
        "stimulus": 2289, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MM"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IIIMM", 
        "correct": "UMM", 
        "incorrect": "MUM", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 0.6893821963996118, 
        "stimulus": 1362, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IUMU"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MM"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MMIIIIUMU", 
        "correct": "MMUIUMU", 
        "incorrect": "MUIIUMU", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 0.8353817195568333, 
        "stimulus": 1683, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UUMIMIU"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IIIIUUMIMIU", 
        "correct": "IUUUMIMIU", 
        "incorrect": "IIIUMIMIU", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 0.8938765246961979, 
        "stimulus": 1571, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "II"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UIIIII", 
        "correct": "UUII", 
        "incorrect": "IUII", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 0.5927763943673646, 
        "stimulus": 1562, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MIIUU"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MIIIMIIUU", 
        "correct": "MUMIIUU", 
        "incorrect": "MIUIIUU", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 0.8434871876938794, 
        "stimulus": 1953, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        9, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IUMUUU"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IUMUUUIII", 
        "correct": "IUMUUUU", 
        "incorrect": "IUMUUUI", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 1.0517333900262917, 
        "stimulus": 2352, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MI"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IIIMI", 
        "correct": "UMI", 
        "incorrect": "MUI", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 0.38735666663124346, 
        "stimulus": 1415, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MU"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MUIII", 
        "correct": "MUU", 
        "incorrect": "UIU", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 0.8024762620110963, 
        "stimulus": 1438, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IIII", 
        "correct": "UI", 
        "incorrect": "II", 
        "length": 4, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 1.244508755675197, 
        "stimulus": 1400, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IUUIU"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IIIIUUIU", 
        "correct": "UIUUIU", 
        "incorrect": "UIIUIU", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 1.1595088736644934, 
        "stimulus": 2071, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IUM"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IIIIUM", 
        "correct": "UIUM", 
        "incorrect": "UIIM", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 0.6820405736549471, 
        "stimulus": 2089, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        10, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        9, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MIUMMMM"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MIUMMMMIIIM", 
        "correct": "MIUMMMMUM", 
        "incorrect": "MIUMMMUIM", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 0.8590634618363578, 
        "stimulus": 2225, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UM"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IIIUM", 
        "correct": "UUM", 
        "incorrect": "UMU", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 0.5590169943749475, 
        "stimulus": 1677, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MII"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IMUII"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IMUIIIIIMII", 
        "correct": "IMUIIUMII", 
        "incorrect": "IMUIIIUII", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 0.7108547991940223, 
        "stimulus": 2271, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MIMM"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UIU"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UIUIIIMIMM", 
        "correct": "UIUUMIMM", 
        "incorrect": "UIUIUIMM", 
        "length": 10, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 0.7835898655287478, 
        "stimulus": 2006, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IU"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MUIII"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MUIIIIIIIU", 
        "correct": "MUIIIUIU", 
        "incorrect": "MUIIIUII", 
        "length": 10, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 0.6762818988758235, 
        "stimulus": 2195, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UMM"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IIIUMM", 
        "correct": "UUMM", 
        "incorrect": "UMUM", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 0.7711153293935721, 
        "stimulus": 1416, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        9, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IUUIUU"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IUUIUUIII", 
        "correct": "IUUIUUU", 
        "incorrect": "IUUIUUI", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 1.1011354987965498, 
        "stimulus": 1963, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IIIII", 
        "correct": "IUI", 
        "incorrect": "III", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 1.13797411292817, 
        "stimulus": 1527, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UI"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UIIIII", 
        "correct": "UIUI", 
        "incorrect": "IUUI", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 0.6852118453605867, 
        "stimulus": 1403, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MMMII"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MMMIIIIIU", 
        "correct": "MMMIIUU", 
        "incorrect": "MMMIIUI", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 0.8249674316755754, 
        "stimulus": 2197, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IM"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UI"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UIIIIIM", 
        "correct": "UIUIM", 
        "incorrect": "UIUII", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 0.6794057224501368, 
        "stimulus": 2129, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MMI"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UIIIMMI", 
        "correct": "UUMMI", 
        "incorrect": "UIUMI", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 0.7479539121788334, 
        "stimulus": 1475, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UU"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MU"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MUIIIUU", 
        "correct": "MUUUU", 
        "incorrect": "MIUUU", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 0.5637878730520296, 
        "stimulus": 2009, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IMIUU"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IIU"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IIUIIIIMIUU", 
        "correct": "IIUUIMIUU", 
        "incorrect": "IIUIIUIUU", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 0.7492750021259112, 
        "stimulus": 1798, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UM"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UMIII"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UMIIIIIIUM", 
        "correct": "UMIIIUUM", 
        "incorrect": "UMIIIUMU", 
        "length": 10, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 0.7771541264656587, 
        "stimulus": 2269, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UI"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MI"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MIIIIUI", 
        "correct": "MIUUI", 
        "incorrect": "MIUIU", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 0.5614044467634272, 
        "stimulus": 1778, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UUM"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IMI"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IMIIIIUUM", 
        "correct": "IMIUUUM", 
        "incorrect": "IMIUIUM", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 0.6227482374146031, 
        "stimulus": 1727, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UUI"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UUIIII", 
        "correct": "UUIU", 
        "incorrect": "UIIU", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 0.6680902771376099, 
        "stimulus": 1384, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IU"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IIIIU", 
        "correct": "UIU", 
        "incorrect": "UUI", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 0.7926809894852417, 
        "stimulus": 1481, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UUUUU"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MI"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MIIIIUUUUU", 
        "correct": "MIUUUUUU", 
        "incorrect": "UMIUUUUU", 
        "length": 10, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 0.8473588457970882, 
        "stimulus": 1682, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IM"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MIIIIM", 
        "correct": "MUIM", 
        "incorrect": "IUIM", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 0.49412071220923015, 
        "stimulus": 1737, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MUU"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MUUIIII", 
        "correct": "MUUUI", 
        "incorrect": "MUIUI", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 0.6719652679685811, 
        "stimulus": 1534, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UIMM"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UI"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UIIIIUIMM", 
        "correct": "UIUUIMM", 
        "incorrect": "UIUIUMM", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 0.7549616581213989, 
        "stimulus": 2259, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IU"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UIIIIU", 
        "correct": "UUIU", 
        "incorrect": "IUIU", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 0.8581957330962535, 
        "stimulus": 2119, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IIM"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UM"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UMIIIIIM", 
        "correct": "UMUIIM", 
        "incorrect": "UUIIIM", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 0.7838614647948486, 
        "stimulus": 1419, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "II"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MIM"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MIMIIIII", 
        "correct": "MIMUII", 
        "incorrect": "MIUIII", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 0.6527230419257363, 
        "stimulus": 2076, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        9, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MMMUMU"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MMMUMUIII", 
        "correct": "MMMUMUU", 
        "incorrect": "MMMUMUI", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 1.124629660429703, 
        "stimulus": 1983, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UUMUII"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MI"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MIIIIUUMUII", 
        "correct": "MIUUUMUII", 
        "incorrect": "IIUUUMUII", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 0.7403623192833628, 
        "stimulus": 1915, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UI"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UIIII", 
        "correct": "UIU", 
        "incorrect": "IUU", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 0.8556492669885859, 
        "stimulus": 1548, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UM"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IIIIUM", 
        "correct": "IUUM", 
        "incorrect": "IUMU", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 0.5510386122332579, 
        "stimulus": 1838, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MUIIMIU"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IIIMUIIMIU", 
        "correct": "UMUIIMIU", 
        "incorrect": "IUUIIMIU", 
        "length": 10, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 1.0537119529859729, 
        "stimulus": 1879, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MIUIMMM"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IIIMIUIMMM", 
        "correct": "UMIUIMMM", 
        "incorrect": "IUIUIMMM", 
        "length": 10, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 0.9486341675936635, 
        "stimulus": 2160, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UUU"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UUUIII", 
        "correct": "UUUU", 
        "incorrect": "UUIU", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 0.8511615814339223, 
        "stimulus": 1608, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UIIIM", 
        "correct": "UUM", 
        "incorrect": "UMU", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 0.6477929206915621, 
        "stimulus": 1594, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MUM"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MUMIIIU", 
        "correct": "MUMUU", 
        "incorrect": "MUUIU", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 0.5564238098345288, 
        "stimulus": 2105, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UU"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UUIIII", 
        "correct": "UUUI", 
        "incorrect": "UIUU", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 0.7898465678196915, 
        "stimulus": 1722, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IIIIU", 
        "correct": "IUU", 
        "incorrect": "IUI", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 0.6606605800231088, 
        "stimulus": 1440, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IUI"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MUI"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MUIIIIIUI", 
        "correct": "MUIUIUI", 
        "incorrect": "MIIUIUI", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 0.5729863456317833, 
        "stimulus": 1474, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UI"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UIIIIU", 
        "correct": "UIUU", 
        "incorrect": "UIUI", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 0.6596865345789159, 
        "stimulus": 1658, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        9, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MUMMUU"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MUMMUUIII", 
        "correct": "MUMMUUU", 
        "incorrect": "MUMMUUI", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 1.0141203586724712, 
        "stimulus": 2338, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UIU"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IIIUIU", 
        "correct": "UUIU", 
        "incorrect": "UIUU", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 1.0153493759909904, 
        "stimulus": 1782, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IMU"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IIIIMU", 
        "correct": "UIMU", 
        "incorrect": "UIIU", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 0.8056202346747366, 
        "stimulus": 1589, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MUM"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MU"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MUIIIMUM", 
        "correct": "MUUMUM", 
        "incorrect": "MUIUUM", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 0.7460939124106369, 
        "stimulus": 1711, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MIIII", 
        "correct": "MUI", 
        "incorrect": "UMI", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 0.3599373348093634, 
        "stimulus": 1492, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IMI"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IU"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IUIIIIMI", 
        "correct": "IUUIMI", 
        "incorrect": "IUMIUI", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 0.4376480439098951, 
        "stimulus": 1624, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UIII"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UIIIIIIU", 
        "correct": "UIIIUU", 
        "incorrect": "UIIIUI", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 0.5922560530372647, 
        "stimulus": 2303, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MM"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IUII"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IUIIIIIMM", 
        "correct": "IUIIUMM", 
        "incorrect": "IUIIUIM", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 0.8355895321084899, 
        "stimulus": 2346, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UIM"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IIIUIM", 
        "correct": "UUIM", 
        "incorrect": "UIUM", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 0.5966569132363732, 
        "stimulus": 1864, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        9, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MI"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IMUUUU"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IMUUUUIIIMI", 
        "correct": "IMUUUUUMI", 
        "incorrect": "IMUUUUIUI", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 0.8674802940747115, 
        "stimulus": 1979, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UII"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MU"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MUIIIUII", 
        "correct": "MUUUII", 
        "incorrect": "MUUIUI", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 0.7840839485222745, 
        "stimulus": 2004, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MUM"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IIIMUM", 
        "correct": "UMUM", 
        "incorrect": "MUUM", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 0.7866107164940528, 
        "stimulus": 1639, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        9, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MUMIUM"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MUMIUMIII", 
        "correct": "MUMIUMU", 
        "incorrect": "MUMIUMI", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 1.1380421883205303, 
        "stimulus": 2060, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MII"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MIIIII", 
        "correct": "MIIU", 
        "incorrect": "IIIU", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 0.9657032613508, 
        "stimulus": 2059, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MIU"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MIUIIIM", 
        "correct": "MIUUM", 
        "incorrect": "MIUMU", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 0.7834712825353282, 
        "stimulus": 2201, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UUU"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UUUIIII", 
        "correct": "UUUUI", 
        "incorrect": "UUIUI", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 0.6607533584211932, 
        "stimulus": 1895, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MUU"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MIIIMUU", 
        "correct": "MUMUU", 
        "incorrect": "MIUUU", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 0.7547019535093153, 
        "stimulus": 1583, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IMM"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IMMIII", 
        "correct": "IMMU", 
        "incorrect": "IMIU", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 0.8866126755496148, 
        "stimulus": 1457, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UM"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MIIIUM", 
        "correct": "MUUM", 
        "incorrect": "UMUM", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 0.7891679680882915, 
        "stimulus": 1909, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UUMU"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MIIIUUMU", 
        "correct": "MUUUMU", 
        "incorrect": "UMUUMU", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 0.47883063023236605, 
        "stimulus": 2328, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MM"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MMI"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MMIIIIMM", 
        "correct": "MMIUMM", 
        "incorrect": "MMIMUM", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 0.5960609662458541, 
        "stimulus": 2218, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UM"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MM"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MMIIIUM", 
        "correct": "MMUUM", 
        "incorrect": "MUIUM", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 0.6684294314313504, 
        "stimulus": 1750, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UIIIU", 
        "correct": "UUU", 
        "incorrect": "UUI", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 0.6354104829555604, 
        "stimulus": 1442, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MIU"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IM"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IMIIIMIU", 
        "correct": "IMUMIU", 
        "incorrect": "IUIMIU", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 0.7251544742188328, 
        "stimulus": 1615, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        10, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        9, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MUMUUMU"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MUMUUMUIII", 
        "correct": "MUMUUMUU", 
        "incorrect": "MUMUUMUI", 
        "length": 10, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 1.2533286792780192, 
        "stimulus": 2283, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IM"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IIM"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IIMIIIIM", 
        "correct": "IIMUIM", 
        "incorrect": "IIUIIM", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 0.5715363383331787, 
        "stimulus": 2036, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "II"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IIIMU"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IIIMUIIIII", 
        "correct": "IIIMUUII", 
        "incorrect": "IIIMIUII", 
        "length": 10, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 0.8049819599708508, 
        "stimulus": 2079, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IU"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MIUMU"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MIUMUIIIIU", 
        "correct": "MIUMUUIU", 
        "incorrect": "MIUMIUIU", 
        "length": 10, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 0.7469104979912761, 
        "stimulus": 2280, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MUM"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IIM"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IIMIIIMUM", 
        "correct": "IIMUMUM", 
        "incorrect": "IIMIUUM", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 0.7050686354705432, 
        "stimulus": 1434, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IM"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IIIIM", 
        "correct": "UIM", 
        "incorrect": "UII", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 0.6123724356957945, 
        "stimulus": 1622, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MUIMIU"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MIIIMUIMIU", 
        "correct": "MUMUIMIU", 
        "incorrect": "MIUUIMIU", 
        "length": 10, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 0.8489539714056006, 
        "stimulus": 1649, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MMM"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MMMIIII", 
        "correct": "MMMUI", 
        "incorrect": "MMIUI", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 0.6386986379190224, 
        "stimulus": 1653, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UIUI"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IIIUIUI", 
        "correct": "UUIUI", 
        "incorrect": "UIUUI", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 0.6888372508881612, 
        "stimulus": 1738, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "II"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IIIII", 
        "correct": "UII", 
        "incorrect": "III", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 1.1117813126172058, 
        "stimulus": 1533, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        10, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        9, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IIUUMMU"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IIUUMMUIII", 
        "correct": "IIUUMMUU", 
        "incorrect": "IIUUMMUI", 
        "length": 10, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 0.9725974398298084, 
        "stimulus": 2101, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MI"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MIIII", 
        "correct": "MIU", 
        "incorrect": "IIU", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 0.834198788693454, 
        "stimulus": 1538, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IIUU"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IIUUIII", 
        "correct": "IIUUU", 
        "incorrect": "IIUUI", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 0.6618910126309928, 
        "stimulus": 1670, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UMM"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IUUII"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IUUIIIIIUMM", 
        "correct": "IUUIIUUMM", 
        "incorrect": "IUUIIUIUM", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 0.81802788485237, 
        "stimulus": 2084, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        9, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UIUMIU"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UIUMIUIIIU", 
        "correct": "UIUMIUUU", 
        "incorrect": "UIUMIUUI", 
        "length": 10, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 0.7355639123867277, 
        "stimulus": 2344, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IIII"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MMI"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MMIIIIIIII", 
        "correct": "MMIUIIII", 
        "incorrect": "MIIUIIII", 
        "length": 10, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 0.7477202057087736, 
        "stimulus": 1792, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IUMIM"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IUMIMIIIU", 
        "correct": "IUMIMUU", 
        "incorrect": "IUMIUIU", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 0.8287929487841078, 
        "stimulus": 2312, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UMIU"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IIIUMIU", 
        "correct": "UUMIU", 
        "incorrect": "UIMIU", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 0.5611233069231943, 
        "stimulus": 1921, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UI"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IIIUI", 
        "correct": "UUI", 
        "incorrect": "UIU", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 0.687913880209092, 
        "stimulus": 1910, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UUMU"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UUU"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UUUIIIUUMU", 
        "correct": "UUUUUUMU", 
        "incorrect": "UUUUIUMU", 
        "length": 10, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 0.6117792768791093, 
        "stimulus": 1931, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UM"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IIUM"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IIUMIIIUM", 
        "correct": "IIUMUUM", 
        "incorrect": "IIUUIUM", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 0.8250066900717649, 
        "stimulus": 2316, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        9, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IM"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MUUMUM"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MUUMUMIIIIM", 
        "correct": "MUUMUMUIM", 
        "incorrect": "MUUMUUIIM", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 0.832942367832785, 
        "stimulus": 1857, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MMMMI"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UM"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UMIIIMMMMI", 
        "correct": "UMUMMMMI", 
        "incorrect": "UMIUMMMI", 
        "length": 10, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 0.805212652431236, 
        "stimulus": 1512, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IIU"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IIUIIIU", 
        "correct": "IIUUU", 
        "incorrect": "IIUUI", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 0.607999616905763, 
        "stimulus": 2141, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UMI"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MIIIUMI", 
        "correct": "MUUMI", 
        "incorrect": "UMUMI", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 0.7477556682298617, 
        "stimulus": 2100, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        9, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UIIIIM"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UIIIIMIIII", 
        "correct": "UIIIIMUI", 
        "incorrect": "UIIIIUII", 
        "length": 10, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 0.9210948307327412, 
        "stimulus": 1926, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MU"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IIIIMU", 
        "correct": "IUMU", 
        "incorrect": "IUIU", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 0.645260260757668, 
        "stimulus": 1746, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UUMUUM"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IIIUUMUUM", 
        "correct": "UUUMUUM", 
        "incorrect": "UIUMUUM", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 0.8113945804352694, 
        "stimulus": 1839, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UIMMI"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IIIUIMMI", 
        "correct": "UUIMMI", 
        "incorrect": "UIIMMI", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 0.7806028257522861, 
        "stimulus": 2296, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MI"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MIIIIU", 
        "correct": "MIUU", 
        "incorrect": "IIUU", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 0.5756559393797829, 
        "stimulus": 1504, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IM"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IMIII", 
        "correct": "IMU", 
        "incorrect": "IIU", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 0.6122033001707553, 
        "stimulus": 1529, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MIIMM"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IIIMIIMM", 
        "correct": "UMIIMM", 
        "incorrect": "UIIIMM", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 0.7455262468173893, 
        "stimulus": 1565, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IU"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IMIU"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IMIUIIIIU", 
        "correct": "IMIUUIU", 
        "incorrect": "IMIIUIU", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 0.7457803271651272, 
        "stimulus": 1496, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "II"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IIIIII", 
        "correct": "IIUI", 
        "incorrect": "IIII", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 1.0256949769600834, 
        "stimulus": 1569, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IIII", 
        "correct": "IU", 
        "incorrect": "II", 
        "length": 4, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 1.1370625232047489, 
        "stimulus": 1383, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MU"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IIIMU", 
        "correct": "UMU", 
        "incorrect": "MUU", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 0.7522254655961215, 
        "stimulus": 1491, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UIIII", 
        "correct": "UUI", 
        "incorrect": "IUU", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 0.6115328298599106, 
        "stimulus": 1470, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UIIII"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UIIIUIIII", 
        "correct": "UUUIIII", 
        "incorrect": "UUIUIII", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 0.7373221682312536, 
        "stimulus": 1859, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UMII"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UMIIIII", 
        "correct": "UMIIU", 
        "incorrect": "UIIIU", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 0.916513752322945, 
        "stimulus": 2245, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IUI"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IIIIUI", 
        "correct": "UIUI", 
        "incorrect": "UUII", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 0.7898465678196915, 
        "stimulus": 1566, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UUI"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IIIUUI", 
        "correct": "UUUI", 
        "incorrect": "UIUI", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 0.6778606925568681, 
        "stimulus": 1956, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UUIMMU"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IIIIUUIMMU", 
        "correct": "IUUUIMMU", 
        "incorrect": "UIIUIMMU", 
        "length": 10, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 0.9275939227872426, 
        "stimulus": 2311, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MMUI"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MMUIIII", 
        "correct": "MMUIU", 
        "incorrect": "MMUII", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 0.8534330215126126, 
        "stimulus": 2055, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IMMUUIUM"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IIIIMMUUIUM", 
        "correct": "UIMMUUIUM", 
        "incorrect": "IIMMUUIUM", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 0.8760837193952524, 
        "stimulus": 1735, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UM"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UMIII", 
        "correct": "UMU", 
        "incorrect": "UIU", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 0.7912569229667034, 
        "stimulus": 1376, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UUMU"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IIIUUMU", 
        "correct": "UUUMU", 
        "incorrect": "UIUMU", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 0.8631849166449378, 
        "stimulus": 2354, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IUM"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IIM"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IIMIIIIUM", 
        "correct": "IIMUIUM", 
        "incorrect": "IIUIIUM", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 0.5857717562543303, 
        "stimulus": 2216, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UIUUM"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MIIIUIUUM", 
        "correct": "MUUIUUM", 
        "incorrect": "UMUIUUM", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 0.8809006785500657, 
        "stimulus": 1495, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MMU"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IIIMMU", 
        "correct": "UMMU", 
        "incorrect": "UIMU", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 0.6411308414256868, 
        "stimulus": 1550, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UUU"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UMU"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UMUIIIUUU", 
        "correct": "UMUUUUU", 
        "incorrect": "UMIUUUU", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 0.6390507645183586, 
        "stimulus": 1704, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MI"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MIIIII", 
        "correct": "MIUI", 
        "incorrect": "IIUI", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 0.5647387932499875, 
        "stimulus": 1818, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MMUII"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MMUIIIII", 
        "correct": "MMUIIU", 
        "incorrect": "MMUIII", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 0.8818843583942751, 
        "stimulus": 1661, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IUUI"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IIIIUUI", 
        "correct": "UIUUI", 
        "incorrect": "UIIUI", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 1.2283405834382797, 
        "stimulus": 1388, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MMUU"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UIIIMMUU", 
        "correct": "UUMMUU", 
        "incorrect": "UIUMUU", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 0.8703124850632538, 
        "stimulus": 2307, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MIMIIM"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MIIIMIMIIM", 
        "correct": "MUMIMIIM", 
        "incorrect": "MIUIMIIM", 
        "length": 10, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 0.8466319241714613, 
        "stimulus": 1753, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MMUM"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MMUMIII", 
        "correct": "MMUMU", 
        "incorrect": "MMUMI", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 1.0223314496033789, 
        "stimulus": 2082, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IMU"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UI"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UIIIIIMU", 
        "correct": "UIUIMU", 
        "incorrect": "UIMIUU", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 0.587037646214377, 
        "stimulus": 2299, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UM"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UMIIIM", 
        "correct": "UMUM", 
        "incorrect": "UMMU", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 0.7355982318486399, 
        "stimulus": 1853, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UU"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IIIIUU", 
        "correct": "IUUU", 
        "incorrect": "IUIU", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 0.840705225694412, 
        "stimulus": 1412, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MM"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MUMMI"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MUMMIIIIMM", 
        "correct": "MUMMIUMM", 
        "incorrect": "MUMMIMUM", 
        "length": 10, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 0.8027711722029797, 
        "stimulus": 1907, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IM"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IUII"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IUIIIIIIM", 
        "correct": "IUIIUIM", 
        "incorrect": "IUIIUII", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 0.7285296058689329, 
        "stimulus": 2184, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UMM"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UMMIII", 
        "correct": "UMMU", 
        "incorrect": "UMIU", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 1.0092116046790147, 
        "stimulus": 2256, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        9, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IIUMUM"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IIUMUMIII", 
        "correct": "IIUMUMU", 
        "incorrect": "IIUMUMI", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 1.0333832234636615, 
        "stimulus": 1483, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IMU"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MIIII"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MIIIIIIIIMU", 
        "correct": "MIIIIUIMU", 
        "incorrect": "MIIIIUIIU", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 0.7997820253529264, 
        "stimulus": 2204, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IIMM"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IIMMIII", 
        "correct": "IIMMU", 
        "incorrect": "IIMIU", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 0.5059939751889266, 
        "stimulus": 1640, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "II"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MIIIII", 
        "correct": "MUII", 
        "incorrect": "IUII", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 0.40200652819702, 
        "stimulus": 1745, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IIIM"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IIIMIII", 
        "correct": "IIIMU", 
        "incorrect": "IIIIU", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 0.40042461180982797, 
        "stimulus": 2237, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IUU"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IUUIII", 
        "correct": "IUUU", 
        "incorrect": "IUUI", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 0.7408001298042767, 
        "stimulus": 1501, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UUUM"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MIIIUUUM", 
        "correct": "MUUUUM", 
        "incorrect": "UMUUUM", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 0.7160309425367177, 
        "stimulus": 1997, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UIM"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UIMIII", 
        "correct": "UIMU", 
        "incorrect": "UIIU", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 0.8732703119361699, 
        "stimulus": 1690, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UUIU"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IIIUUIU", 
        "correct": "UUUIU", 
        "incorrect": "UIUIU", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 1.1297006767666908, 
        "stimulus": 1766, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UIMU"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UIMUIII", 
        "correct": "UIMUU", 
        "incorrect": "UIMUI", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 0.5460840118911013, 
        "stimulus": 1500, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IMIIM"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MIIIIMIIM", 
        "correct": "MUIMIIM", 
        "incorrect": "UMIMIIM", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 0.7736712654596484, 
        "stimulus": 1360, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UUIUM"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MM"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MMIIIUUIUM", 
        "correct": "MMUUUIUM", 
        "incorrect": "MUIUUIUM", 
        "length": 10, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 0.7168769336123992, 
        "stimulus": 2295, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MM"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MMIIII", 
        "correct": "MMUI", 
        "incorrect": "MIUI", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 0.6378286732592467, 
        "stimulus": 2181, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MMU"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MMUIII", 
        "correct": "MMUU", 
        "incorrect": "MMUI", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 0.7267871892141525, 
        "stimulus": 1597, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IUU"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UMII"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UMIIIIIIUU", 
        "correct": "UMIIUIUU", 
        "incorrect": "UMIIUIIU", 
        "length": 10, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 0.8034501612070879, 
        "stimulus": 1862, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IMMIUM"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UI"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UIIIIIMMIUM", 
        "correct": "UIUIMMIUM", 
        "incorrect": "UIIIUMIUM", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 0.881735826652617, 
        "stimulus": 1924, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MMI"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UU"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UUIIIMMI", 
        "correct": "UUUMMI", 
        "incorrect": "UUIUMI", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 0.8051431545548419, 
        "stimulus": 2063, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "II"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MI"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MIIIIII", 
        "correct": "MIUII", 
        "incorrect": "IIUII", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 0.5623057891389708, 
        "stimulus": 1712, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UI"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UM"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UMIIIUI", 
        "correct": "UMUUI", 
        "incorrect": "UUIUI", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 0.7079969683666254, 
        "stimulus": 1903, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UUIU"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MIIIUUIU", 
        "correct": "MUUUIU", 
        "incorrect": "UMUUIU", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 0.7513910793149745, 
        "stimulus": 2047, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "II"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IMIU"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IMIUIIIII", 
        "correct": "IMIUUII", 
        "incorrect": "IMIIUII", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 0.6728004571134627, 
        "stimulus": 2230, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MUIU"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IIIMUIU", 
        "correct": "UMUIU", 
        "incorrect": "IUUIU", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 0.8921459373640178, 
        "stimulus": 1933, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IM"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UM"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UMIIIIM", 
        "correct": "UMUIM", 
        "incorrect": "UUIIM", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 0.670636637686703, 
        "stimulus": 2270, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UI"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IIIIUI", 
        "correct": "IUUI", 
        "incorrect": "IUIU", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 0.6821380191378962, 
        "stimulus": 1717, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UUUIM"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IIIUUUIM", 
        "correct": "UUUUIM", 
        "incorrect": "UIUUIM", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 1.0146474953467823, 
        "stimulus": 2175, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MMM"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UIM"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UIMIIIMMM", 
        "correct": "UIMUMMM", 
        "incorrect": "UIUIMMM", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 0.6637388771813864, 
        "stimulus": 1573, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UMUM"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UMUMIII", 
        "correct": "UMUMU", 
        "incorrect": "UMUMI", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 0.8315711918411126, 
        "stimulus": 2148, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UIUM"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UIMU"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UIMUIIIUIUM", 
        "correct": "UIMUUUIUM", 
        "incorrect": "UIMUUIUUM", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 0.6871379493980923, 
        "stimulus": 1370, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IIUII"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IIUIIIII", 
        "correct": "IIUIIU", 
        "incorrect": "IIUIII", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 0.6834878288930228, 
        "stimulus": 2260, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IIM"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IIMIIII", 
        "correct": "IIMUI", 
        "incorrect": "IIIUI", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 0.3598653247009543, 
        "stimulus": 1858, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MUI"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MM"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MMIIIMUI", 
        "correct": "MMUMUI", 
        "incorrect": "MUIMUI", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 0.5129073791551813, 
        "stimulus": 1431, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MUIM"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MIIIMUIM", 
        "correct": "MUMUIM", 
        "incorrect": "MIUUIM", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 0.7819695824977795, 
        "stimulus": 1820, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UU"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UUIII", 
        "correct": "UUU", 
        "incorrect": "UIU", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 0.61509605029727, 
        "stimulus": 1613, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UUI"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IM"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IMIIIUUI", 
        "correct": "IMUUUI", 
        "incorrect": "IUIUUI", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 0.6224655913538278, 
        "stimulus": 1636, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MMI"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IIIIMMI", 
        "correct": "IUMMI", 
        "incorrect": "IIUMI", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 0.6475998536855004, 
        "stimulus": 1762, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UUM"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UUMIIII", 
        "correct": "UUMUI", 
        "incorrect": "UUUMI", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 0.6985284053745366, 
        "stimulus": 1497, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IMMUU"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IIIIMMUU", 
        "correct": "UIMMUU", 
        "incorrect": "UIIMUU", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 0.8150101440259212, 
        "stimulus": 1530, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UUUU"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "II"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IIIIIUUUU", 
        "correct": "IIUUUUU", 
        "incorrect": "IUIIUUU", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 0.7804402629157081, 
        "stimulus": 1560, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MI"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IIIIMI", 
        "correct": "IUMI", 
        "incorrect": "IUII", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 0.6621911994485196, 
        "stimulus": 1856, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        9, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MM"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UMIUIM"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UMIUIMIIIMM", 
        "correct": "UMIUIMUMM", 
        "incorrect": "UMIUIUIMM", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 0.9581239325456934, 
        "stimulus": 2243, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UI"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MU"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MUIIIUI", 
        "correct": "MUUUI", 
        "incorrect": "MIUUI", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 0.6858665134979115, 
        "stimulus": 1938, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MM"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IM"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IMIIIMM", 
        "correct": "IMUMM", 
        "incorrect": "IUIMM", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 0.6581427117477866, 
        "stimulus": 1912, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IIMM"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MM"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MMIIIIIMM", 
        "correct": "MMUIIMM", 
        "incorrect": "MUIIIMM", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 0.7131075453560898, 
        "stimulus": 1830, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UM"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MUMMU"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MUMMUIIIUM", 
        "correct": "MUMMUUUM", 
        "incorrect": "MUMMUUMU", 
        "length": 10, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 0.7392817085923099, 
        "stimulus": 1535, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IMM"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UUUM"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UUUMIIIIMM", 
        "correct": "UUUMUIMM", 
        "incorrect": "UUUUIIMM", 
        "length": 10, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 0.7766442756212698, 
        "stimulus": 1733, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UIMMM"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MIIIUIMMM", 
        "correct": "MUUIMMM", 
        "incorrect": "UMUIMMM", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 0.8546591561685432, 
        "stimulus": 1809, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        10, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        9, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MMUMMIM"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MMUMMIMIIIU", 
        "correct": "MMUMMIMUU", 
        "incorrect": "MMUMMIUIU", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 1.0770180728138412, 
        "stimulus": 1972, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UUUUI"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UUUUIIII", 
        "correct": "UUUUIU", 
        "incorrect": "UUUUII", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 1.1368788986127052, 
        "stimulus": 2324, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IIM"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IM"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IMIIIIIM", 
        "correct": "IMUIIM", 
        "incorrect": "IUIIIM", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 0.693823365413889, 
        "stimulus": 2322, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IMIMIUUU"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IIIIMIMIUUU", 
        "correct": "UIMIMIUUU", 
        "incorrect": "UIIIMIUUU", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 1.1292222736563833, 
        "stimulus": 1477, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MU"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MUIIIM", 
        "correct": "MUUM", 
        "incorrect": "MUMU", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 0.5571315031751469, 
        "stimulus": 1511, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IUMI"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UIIIIUMI", 
        "correct": "UUIUMI", 
        "incorrect": "IUIUMI", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 0.7416182553721655, 
        "stimulus": 2008, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IU"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IUIIIU", 
        "correct": "IUUU", 
        "incorrect": "IUUI", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 0.5267287117105959, 
        "stimulus": 2120, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IMI"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MUII"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MUIIIIIIMI", 
        "correct": "MUIIUIMI", 
        "incorrect": "MUIIMIUI", 
        "length": 10, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 0.631219608281984, 
        "stimulus": 1424, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UIUMIU"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UIIIUIUMIU", 
        "correct": "UUUIUMIU", 
        "incorrect": "IUUIUMIU", 
        "length": 10, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 0.7221742371006329, 
        "stimulus": 2250, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IU"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IUU"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IUUIIIIU", 
        "correct": "IUUUIU", 
        "incorrect": "IUIIUU", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 0.6424596452493669, 
        "stimulus": 1634, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MII"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UIIIMII", 
        "correct": "UUMII", 
        "incorrect": "UIUII", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 0.2498425916961016, 
        "stimulus": 1719, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MUU"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IIIMUU", 
        "correct": "UMUU", 
        "incorrect": "MUUU", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 0.6804261596226628, 
        "stimulus": 1610, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MMM"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IIIMMM", 
        "correct": "UMMM", 
        "incorrect": "UIMM", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 0.7607604217513467, 
        "stimulus": 1790, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IUUIU"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IUUIUIII", 
        "correct": "IUUIUU", 
        "incorrect": "IUUIUI", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 0.9648955780087649, 
        "stimulus": 1694, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MMIMIUU"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IIIMMIMIUU", 
        "correct": "UMMIMIUU", 
        "incorrect": "IUMIMIUU", 
        "length": 10, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 0.8602511727522781, 
        "stimulus": 2030, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IIIIM", 
        "correct": "IUM", 
        "incorrect": "IMU", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 1.0565309205934044, 
        "stimulus": 1418, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MU"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MIIIMU", 
        "correct": "MUMU", 
        "incorrect": "UMMU", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 0.3201562118716424, 
        "stimulus": 1805, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MII"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IIIIMII", 
        "correct": "IUMII", 
        "incorrect": "IIUII", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 0.5590169943749475, 
        "stimulus": 1914, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        9, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IUUMUU"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IUUMUUIIIM", 
        "correct": "IUUMUUUM", 
        "incorrect": "IUUMUUMU", 
        "length": 10, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 0.921126788684575, 
        "stimulus": 1811, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UU"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MM"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MMIIIUU", 
        "correct": "MMUUU", 
        "incorrect": "MUIUU", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 0.7801860457062465, 
        "stimulus": 1638, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MM"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IUIU"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IUIUIIIMM", 
        "correct": "IUIUUMM", 
        "incorrect": "IUIUMUM", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 0.7715207403812219, 
        "stimulus": 1896, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MIUI"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IIIMIUI", 
        "correct": "UMIUI", 
        "incorrect": "IUIUI", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 0.8939959500086901, 
        "stimulus": 2077, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UIIM"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UIIMIII", 
        "correct": "UIIMU", 
        "incorrect": "UIIIU", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 0.9392552763360648, 
        "stimulus": 1741, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MIIUUII"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MIIIMIIUUII", 
        "correct": "MUMIIUUII", 
        "incorrect": "MIUIIUUII", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 0.6763929933456286, 
        "stimulus": 1927, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IUUU"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IIIIUUU", 
        "correct": "UIUUU", 
        "incorrect": "UIIUU", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 0.9545763394877307, 
        "stimulus": 1473, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UIM"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UM"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UMIIIUIM", 
        "correct": "UMUUIM", 
        "incorrect": "UUIUIM", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 0.7245294921590215, 
        "stimulus": 1962, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MIMUM"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UII"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UIIIIIMIMUM", 
        "correct": "UIIUMIMUM", 
        "incorrect": "UIIIUIMUM", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 0.7639945088554946, 
        "stimulus": 1699, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MI"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UIIIMI", 
        "correct": "UUMI", 
        "incorrect": "UMUI", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 0.9458357665468693, 
        "stimulus": 1860, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IUI"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UIIIIUI", 
        "correct": "UUIUI", 
        "incorrect": "IUIUI", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 0.9119797292430286, 
        "stimulus": 1575, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MMI"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UIUMI"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UIUMIIIIMMI", 
        "correct": "UIUMIUMMI", 
        "incorrect": "UIUMIIUMI", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 0.8518553807525321, 
        "stimulus": 2349, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MUI"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IIIMUI", 
        "correct": "UMUI", 
        "incorrect": "MUUI", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 0.757544084751347, 
        "stimulus": 1696, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UIII"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UIIIIIII", 
        "correct": "UIIIUI", 
        "incorrect": "IIIIUI", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 0.7162080677002916, 
        "stimulus": 1537, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MUMUMU"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "II"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IIIIIMUMUMU", 
        "correct": "IIUMUMUMU", 
        "incorrect": "IIIUUMUMU", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 0.9156057460606533, 
        "stimulus": 2257, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IUM"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IIIIIUM", 
        "correct": "IUIUM", 
        "incorrect": "IUUIM", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 0.6766630927935858, 
        "stimulus": 2158, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MUUIUM"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MU"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MUIIIMUUIUM", 
        "correct": "MUUMUUIUM", 
        "incorrect": "MUIUUUIUM", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 0.8464376387629747, 
        "stimulus": 2332, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MUIUMIM"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IIIMUIUMIM", 
        "correct": "UMUIUMIM", 
        "incorrect": "IUUIUMIM", 
        "length": 10, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 1.0462202853827163, 
        "stimulus": 1777, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UI"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IMI"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IMIIIIUI", 
        "correct": "IMIUUI", 
        "incorrect": "IMIUIU", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 0.6534769603193413, 
        "stimulus": 2136, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MIUMMU"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IIIMIUMMU", 
        "correct": "UMIUMMU", 
        "incorrect": "IUIUMMU", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 1.014962131770804, 
        "stimulus": 2273, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MM"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UIIIMM", 
        "correct": "UUMM", 
        "incorrect": "UMUM", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 0.5249272661725857, 
        "stimulus": 2023, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MM"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UUMMM"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UUMMMIIIMM", 
        "correct": "UUMMMUMM", 
        "incorrect": "UUMMUIMM", 
        "length": 10, 
        "rule": "III=U", 
        "score": 0.83861853015509, 
        "stimulus": 1642, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UUI", 
        "correct": "I", 
        "incorrect": "U", 
        "length": 3, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 0.7309682448990257, 
        "stimulus": 2361, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UUM", 
        "correct": "M", 
        "incorrect": "U", 
        "length": 3, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 0.7309682448990257, 
        "stimulus": 2359, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MU"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MUUMU", 
        "correct": "MMU", 
        "incorrect": "UMU", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 0.506006251548276, 
        "stimulus": 2404, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MUU", 
        "correct": "M", 
        "incorrect": "U", 
        "length": 3, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 0.7309682448990257, 
        "stimulus": 2403, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UI"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UIUU", 
        "correct": "UI", 
        "incorrect": "UU", 
        "length": 4, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 0.7567779351176517, 
        "stimulus": 2431, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MI"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MIM"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MIMUUMI", 
        "correct": "MIMMI", 
        "incorrect": "MIUMI", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 0.30960252623162815, 
        "stimulus": 3228, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IU"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IUUU", 
        "correct": "IU", 
        "incorrect": "UU", 
        "length": 4, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 0.7791196430149214, 
        "stimulus": 2358, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        9, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MI"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UMIMMII"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UMIMMIIUUMI", 
        "correct": "UMIMMIIMI", 
        "incorrect": "UMIMMIUMI", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 1.1908978374927939, 
        "stimulus": 2988, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MMM"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UUMMM", 
        "correct": "MMM", 
        "incorrect": "UMM", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 0.8454287726350072, 
        "stimulus": 2512, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UUII"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UUIIUUU", 
        "correct": "UUIIU", 
        "incorrect": "UUIUU", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 0.7910096882437057, 
        "stimulus": 2390, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "II"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MUUII", 
        "correct": "MII", 
        "incorrect": "UII", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 0.5198024370057511, 
        "stimulus": 3084, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MIM"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "II"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IIUUMIM", 
        "correct": "IIMIM", 
        "incorrect": "IIUIM", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 0.8129297639326244, 
        "stimulus": 3290, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MUUIUI"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IM"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IMUUMUUIUI", 
        "correct": "IMMUUIUI", 
        "incorrect": "IUMUUIUI", 
        "length": 10, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 0.9929213908520385, 
        "stimulus": 2911, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MM"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UIMM"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UIMMUUMM", 
        "correct": "UIMMMM", 
        "incorrect": "UIMUMM", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 0.7264835461573471, 
        "stimulus": 3001, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UMM"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UMMUU", 
        "correct": "UMM", 
        "incorrect": "UMU", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 0.82915619758885, 
        "stimulus": 3022, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UUUI"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UUUIUUU", 
        "correct": "UUUIU", 
        "incorrect": "UUUUU", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 0.5432094862033506, 
        "stimulus": 3272, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MI"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MIUU", 
        "correct": "MI", 
        "incorrect": "MU", 
        "length": 4, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 0.9518645788210999, 
        "stimulus": 2402, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MUMMU"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UUUMUMMU", 
        "correct": "UMUMMU", 
        "incorrect": "UUUMMU", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 0.8428062414041227, 
        "stimulus": 2690, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IU"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UI"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UIUUIU", 
        "correct": "UIIU", 
        "incorrect": "UUUU", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 0.524443838692486, 
        "stimulus": 2433, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UI"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UUUI", 
        "correct": "UI", 
        "incorrect": "UU", 
        "length": 4, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 1.0026273638939205, 
        "stimulus": 2426, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IMI"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IMIUUM", 
        "correct": "IMIM", 
        "incorrect": "IMIU", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 0.8284591833070646, 
        "stimulus": 2680, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IUU", 
        "correct": "I", 
        "incorrect": "U", 
        "length": 3, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 0.7309682448990257, 
        "stimulus": 2461, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UM"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UUUM", 
        "correct": "UM", 
        "incorrect": "UU", 
        "length": 4, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 0.7791196430149214, 
        "stimulus": 2377, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MI"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UUMI", 
        "correct": "MI", 
        "incorrect": "UI", 
        "length": 4, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 0.7970024109630638, 
        "stimulus": 2546, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UIM"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UUUIM", 
        "correct": "UIM", 
        "incorrect": "UUM", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 0.7586877434475693, 
        "stimulus": 2861, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IUM"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IUUIUM", 
        "correct": "IIUM", 
        "incorrect": "UUUM", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 0.7647948072653822, 
        "stimulus": 2458, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IU"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UUIU", 
        "correct": "IU", 
        "incorrect": "UU", 
        "length": 4, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 0.7567779351176517, 
        "stimulus": 2465, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MUUI", 
        "correct": "MI", 
        "incorrect": "UI", 
        "length": 4, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 0.5798224597222542, 
        "stimulus": 2383, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UII"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UM"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UMUUUII", 
        "correct": "UMUII", 
        "incorrect": "UMUUI", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 1.0557443019503325, 
        "stimulus": 3221, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MIIUM"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MIIUMUUM", 
        "correct": "MIIUMM", 
        "incorrect": "MIIUMU", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 1.1737308160461388, 
        "stimulus": 3219, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MU"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MUU"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MUUUUMU", 
        "correct": "MUUMU", 
        "incorrect": "UUUMU", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 0.9352090209159658, 
        "stimulus": 2446, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IMM"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IMMUU", 
        "correct": "IMM", 
        "incorrect": "IMU", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 0.8394386740705845, 
        "stimulus": 2569, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IMU"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UI"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UIUUIMU", 
        "correct": "UIIMU", 
        "incorrect": "UIUMU", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 0.754858965358655, 
        "stimulus": 3306, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MMU"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IMU"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IMUUUMMU", 
        "correct": "IMUMMU", 
        "incorrect": "IUUMMU", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 0.5586946078851217, 
        "stimulus": 2837, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MU"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MUUU", 
        "correct": "MU", 
        "incorrect": "UU", 
        "length": 4, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 0.8656620411877809, 
        "stimulus": 2372, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IUUI", 
        "correct": "II", 
        "incorrect": "UI", 
        "length": 4, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 0.5231578010489428, 
        "stimulus": 2362, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UUM"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UUMUU", 
        "correct": "UUM", 
        "incorrect": "UUU", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 0.5679722898819567, 
        "stimulus": 2380, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MIMUI"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MIMUIUU", 
        "correct": "MIMUI", 
        "incorrect": "MIMUU", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 0.9839580948151601, 
        "stimulus": 3199, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MMUIIM"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MMUIIMUUI", 
        "correct": "MMUIIMI", 
        "incorrect": "MMUIIMU", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 1.0400746649827253, 
        "stimulus": 3051, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UUM"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IIUIUI"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IIUIUIUUUUM", 
        "correct": "IIUIUIUUM", 
        "incorrect": "IIUIUIUUU", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 0.823252408520673, 
        "stimulus": 2983, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IUII"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IUIIUUU", 
        "correct": "IUIIU", 
        "incorrect": "IUIUU", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 0.754386477039807, 
        "stimulus": 2914, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MUUU"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UI"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UIUUMUUU", 
        "correct": "UIMUUU", 
        "incorrect": "UMIUUU", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 0.4300569492425819, 
        "stimulus": 3226, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "II"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IIUU", 
        "correct": "II", 
        "incorrect": "IU", 
        "length": 4, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 0.4892642534945744, 
        "stimulus": 2396, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IU"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IIMU"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IIMUUUIU", 
        "correct": "IIMUIU", 
        "incorrect": "IIUUIU", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 0.5004435992873966, 
        "stimulus": 2795, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MUI"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IUIUUM"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IUIUUMUUMUI", 
        "correct": "IUIUUMMUI", 
        "incorrect": "IUIUUUMUI", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 0.8924644311101506, 
        "stimulus": 3188, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        9, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MM"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IUMIUIM"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IUMIUIMUUMM", 
        "correct": "IUMIUIMMM", 
        "incorrect": "IUMIUIUMM", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 0.8938525771552801, 
        "stimulus": 3017, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MMMIU"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UMM"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UMMUUMMMIU", 
        "correct": "UMMMMMIU", 
        "incorrect": "UMMUMMIU", 
        "length": 10, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 0.700985103503828, 
        "stimulus": 3313, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UIM"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UIMUU", 
        "correct": "UIM", 
        "incorrect": "UIU", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 0.7296453628256862, 
        "stimulus": 2553, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UM"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UMI"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UMIUUUM", 
        "correct": "UMIUM", 
        "incorrect": "UMIUU", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 0.6572697945183967, 
        "stimulus": 3140, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MIIU"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MIIUUUI", 
        "correct": "MIIUI", 
        "incorrect": "MIIUU", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 1.1637387518660371, 
        "stimulus": 2771, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        9, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UM"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MMIMIUU"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MMIMIUUUUUM", 
        "correct": "MMIMIUUUM", 
        "incorrect": "MMIMIUUUU", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 1.3546161446096936, 
        "stimulus": 3100, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IM"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MIIIII"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MIIIIIUUIM", 
        "correct": "MIIIIIIM", 
        "incorrect": "MIIIIUIM", 
        "length": 10, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 0.645801619539647, 
        "stimulus": 2863, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IMIUII"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IMIUIIUUU", 
        "correct": "IMIUIIU", 
        "incorrect": "IMIUIUU", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 1.1036887755374634, 
        "stimulus": 3044, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "III"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UI"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UIUUIII", 
        "correct": "UIIII", 
        "incorrect": "UIUII", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 0.2732670913442732, 
        "stimulus": 3132, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UUIII"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UUUUIII", 
        "correct": "UUIII", 
        "incorrect": "UUUII", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 1.0915177829430953, 
        "stimulus": 3253, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        9, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UUMMIUU"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UUMMIUUUUU", 
        "correct": "UUMMIUUU", 
        "incorrect": "UUMIUUUU", 
        "length": 10, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 0.9266458159802483, 
        "stimulus": 3024, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IIIIMUMI"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MUUIIIIMUMI", 
        "correct": "MIIIIMUMI", 
        "incorrect": "MUIIIMUMI", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 1.1462588763796808, 
        "stimulus": 3220, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MUUI"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UUMUUI", 
        "correct": "MUUI", 
        "incorrect": "UUUI", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 1.0522916282213945, 
        "stimulus": 2868, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MIM"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UUUMIM", 
        "correct": "UMIM", 
        "incorrect": "UUIM", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 1.0661614034159137, 
        "stimulus": 2658, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MMUUIUU"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UUMMUUIUU", 
        "correct": "MMUUIUU", 
        "incorrect": "UMUUIUU", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 1.1291401290427163, 
        "stimulus": 3325, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IM"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IMIMI"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IMIMIUUIM", 
        "correct": "IMIMIIM", 
        "incorrect": "IMIMUIM", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 0.9936207228158765, 
        "stimulus": 2640, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UI"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UUUUI", 
        "correct": "UUI", 
        "incorrect": "UUU", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 1.0223573426124228, 
        "stimulus": 2522, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MU"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UUMU", 
        "correct": "MU", 
        "incorrect": "UU", 
        "length": 4, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 0.7567779351176517, 
        "stimulus": 2421, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UUM"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UUMUUU", 
        "correct": "UUMU", 
        "incorrect": "UUUM", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 0.6269939261394298, 
        "stimulus": 2900, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UMIMM"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UUUMIMM", 
        "correct": "UMIMM", 
        "incorrect": "UUIMM", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 1.050702772719268, 
        "stimulus": 3240, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IMIM"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UUIMIM", 
        "correct": "IMIM", 
        "incorrect": "UMIM", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 0.9720943646281776, 
        "stimulus": 3092, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MUIM"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UII"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UIIUUMUIM", 
        "correct": "UIIMUIM", 
        "incorrect": "UIUMUIM", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 0.6423987836500745, 
        "stimulus": 2934, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "II"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UUUII", 
        "correct": "UII", 
        "incorrect": "UUI", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 0.8412458460623256, 
        "stimulus": 2462, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IUUM", 
        "correct": "IM", 
        "incorrect": "UM", 
        "length": 4, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 0.8072943667639517, 
        "stimulus": 2567, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UUMUU"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UUUUMUU", 
        "correct": "UUMUU", 
        "incorrect": "UUUUU", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 0.6102025668482818, 
        "stimulus": 2487, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UIU"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UUUIU", 
        "correct": "UIU", 
        "incorrect": "UUU", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 0.7472949916413087, 
        "stimulus": 2517, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UIMM"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MMM"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MMMUUUIMM", 
        "correct": "MMMUIMM", 
        "incorrect": "MMUUIMM", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 0.8206723423195853, 
        "stimulus": 3016, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IUUU"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MUUIUUU", 
        "correct": "MIUUU", 
        "incorrect": "IMUUU", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 0.5579895193957818, 
        "stimulus": 2849, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UUM"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IIU"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IIUUUUUM", 
        "correct": "IIUUUM", 
        "incorrect": "IIUUUU", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 1.057203251561909, 
        "stimulus": 3201, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MMMI"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UUUMMMI", 
        "correct": "UMMMI", 
        "incorrect": "UUMMI", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 1.1970158354727392, 
        "stimulus": 2429, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IMU"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IMUUUM", 
        "correct": "IMUM", 
        "incorrect": "IMUU", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 0.8606747111123451, 
        "stimulus": 2966, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MMU"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MUUMMU", 
        "correct": "MMMU", 
        "incorrect": "MUMU", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 0.5082441740734092, 
        "stimulus": 2753, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IIUM"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IIUMUUM", 
        "correct": "IIUMM", 
        "incorrect": "IIUMU", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 0.9294201174226219, 
        "stimulus": 2784, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IM"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UUIM", 
        "correct": "IM", 
        "incorrect": "UM", 
        "length": 4, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 0.5231578010489428, 
        "stimulus": 2612, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MUM"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UUMUM", 
        "correct": "MUM", 
        "incorrect": "UMM", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 0.6262246302449154, 
        "stimulus": 2673, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IIIIM"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UUIIIIM", 
        "correct": "IIIIM", 
        "incorrect": "UIIIM", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 1.011610861747669, 
        "stimulus": 3216, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IMM"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UUIMM", 
        "correct": "IMM", 
        "incorrect": "UMM", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 0.7042370371772445, 
        "stimulus": 2710, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MMU"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MMUUUU", 
        "correct": "MMUU", 
        "incorrect": "MUUU", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 0.9277720400768277, 
        "stimulus": 2895, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MM"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MMUUI", 
        "correct": "MMI", 
        "incorrect": "MUI", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 0.8155795902468446, 
        "stimulus": 2568, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UUMMMI"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MM"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MMUUUUMMMI", 
        "correct": "MMUUMMMI", 
        "incorrect": "MMUUUMMI", 
        "length": 10, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 1.019804738043465, 
        "stimulus": 2725, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "II"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IIUUI", 
        "correct": "III", 
        "incorrect": "IUI", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 0.7113665205827001, 
        "stimulus": 2979, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IMUU"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IMUUUU", 
        "correct": "IMUU", 
        "incorrect": "IUUU", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 0.9037098421585796, 
        "stimulus": 2637, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MII"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IUUMII"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IUUMIIUUMII", 
        "correct": "IUUMIIMII", 
        "incorrect": "IUUMIUMII", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 0.8191444090961739, 
        "stimulus": 2962, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MI"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MIUUM", 
        "correct": "MIM", 
        "incorrect": "MIU", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 0.6992031457885156, 
        "stimulus": 2387, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IIUU"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IU"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IUUUIIUU", 
        "correct": "IUIIUU", 
        "incorrect": "IUUIUU", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 0.8005805282933273, 
        "stimulus": 2651, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UM"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UMUUM", 
        "correct": "UMM", 
        "incorrect": "UMU", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 0.6262246302449154, 
        "stimulus": 3287, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IMU"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IMUUU", 
        "correct": "IMU", 
        "incorrect": "IUU", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 0.9141660757932982, 
        "stimulus": 2694, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "II"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IUUII", 
        "correct": "III", 
        "incorrect": "IUI", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 0.506006251548276, 
        "stimulus": 2369, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UUUIII"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UUUIIIUUM", 
        "correct": "UUUIIIM", 
        "incorrect": "UUUIIIU", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 0.3877100821645857, 
        "stimulus": 2442, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IIIIUM"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IIIIUMUUI", 
        "correct": "IIIIUMI", 
        "incorrect": "IIIIUMU", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 0.928100061151558, 
        "stimulus": 3054, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UMU"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UMUUUI", 
        "correct": "UMUI", 
        "incorrect": "UMUU", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 0.46550131988457855, 
        "stimulus": 3058, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UIM"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UIMUUM", 
        "correct": "UIMM", 
        "incorrect": "UIMU", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 0.8766379762553461, 
        "stimulus": 3248, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UMMM"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UMMMUUI", 
        "correct": "UMMMI", 
        "incorrect": "UMMMU", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 0.5552172539775081, 
        "stimulus": 2792, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IMMUIUM"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IUUIMMUIUM", 
        "correct": "IIMMUIUM", 
        "incorrect": "IUMMUIUM", 
        "length": 10, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 1.0368077186485, 
        "stimulus": 2984, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UI"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UIUUM", 
        "correct": "UIM", 
        "incorrect": "UIU", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 0.3901920163190612, 
        "stimulus": 2548, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MU"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IUUMU", 
        "correct": "IMU", 
        "incorrect": "MIU", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 0.526545163874035, 
        "stimulus": 2549, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MMMUM"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UM"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UMUUMMMUM", 
        "correct": "UMMMMUM", 
        "incorrect": "UMUMMUM", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 0.5802723390239999, 
        "stimulus": 3291, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        9, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        10, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MIIIMIUM"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MIIIMIUMUU", 
        "correct": "MIIIMIUM", 
        "incorrect": "MIIIMIUU", 
        "length": 10, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 0.8047624058479773, 
        "stimulus": 3038, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UMU"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UMUUU", 
        "correct": "UMU", 
        "incorrect": "UUM", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 0.8394386740705845, 
        "stimulus": 3334, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UM"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UMUU", 
        "correct": "UM", 
        "incorrect": "UU", 
        "length": 4, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 0.7567779351176517, 
        "stimulus": 2366, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UMM"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IUUUMM", 
        "correct": "IUMM", 
        "incorrect": "IUUM", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 1.032093878779953, 
        "stimulus": 2502, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        9, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IIIMUII"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IIIMUIIUU", 
        "correct": "IIIMUII", 
        "incorrect": "IIIMUIU", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 1.2018992329825344, 
        "stimulus": 2884, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MUI"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MM"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MMUUMUI", 
        "correct": "MMMUI", 
        "incorrect": "MUMUI", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 0.7423799684387966, 
        "stimulus": 2526, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IMI"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IMIUUI", 
        "correct": "IMII", 
        "incorrect": "IMIU", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 0.7863282650900716, 
        "stimulus": 2800, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MI"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MIUUU", 
        "correct": "MIU", 
        "incorrect": "MUU", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 0.9008257825594918, 
        "stimulus": 2646, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MUUM", 
        "correct": "MM", 
        "incorrect": "UM", 
        "length": 4, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 0.5231578010489428, 
        "stimulus": 2411, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "II"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UUII", 
        "correct": "II", 
        "incorrect": "UI", 
        "length": 4, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 0.8182465509439674, 
        "stimulus": 2394, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UIIIMIUIU"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UUUIIIMIUIU", 
        "correct": "UIIIMIUIU", 
        "incorrect": "UUIIMIUIU", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 1.3840900622430266, 
        "stimulus": 3205, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UUUI", 
        "correct": "UI", 
        "incorrect": "UU", 
        "length": 4, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 0.7791196430149214, 
        "stimulus": 2630, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MUII"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MUIIUUM", 
        "correct": "MUIIM", 
        "incorrect": "MUIIU", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 0.9784379258420398, 
        "stimulus": 2365, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IM"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IMUU", 
        "correct": "IM", 
        "incorrect": "IU", 
        "length": 4, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 0.8076943299332474, 
        "stimulus": 2427, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MIIM"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UUMIIM", 
        "correct": "MIIM", 
        "incorrect": "UIIM", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 0.9300059662282244, 
        "stimulus": 2514, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IIUM"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UUIIUM", 
        "correct": "IIUM", 
        "incorrect": "UIUM", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 1.1054727280387873, 
        "stimulus": 2716, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UIIMU"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UIIMUUUM", 
        "correct": "UIIMUM", 
        "incorrect": "UIIMUU", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 1.1268982803865428, 
        "stimulus": 3232, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IUUU"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UUIUUU", 
        "correct": "IUUU", 
        "incorrect": "UUUU", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 0.5128633944258288, 
        "stimulus": 2944, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IUUIUMIU"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UUIUUIUMIU", 
        "correct": "IUUIUMIU", 
        "incorrect": "UUUIUMIU", 
        "length": 10, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 1.2189584564117966, 
        "stimulus": 3320, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IIU"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UUUIIU", 
        "correct": "UIIU", 
        "incorrect": "UUIU", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 0.6435541947713397, 
        "stimulus": 2609, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MM"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UUMMU"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UUMMUUUMM", 
        "correct": "UUMMUMM", 
        "incorrect": "UUMMUUM", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 0.46174104099633706, 
        "stimulus": 2738, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "III"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IIIUUM", 
        "correct": "IIIM", 
        "incorrect": "IIUM", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 0.7020994054593264, 
        "stimulus": 2676, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UM"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UMUUU", 
        "correct": "UMU", 
        "incorrect": "UUM", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 0.7261196937138771, 
        "stimulus": 2373, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IMUM"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UUIMUM", 
        "correct": "IMUM", 
        "incorrect": "UMUM", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 0.6874536508549166, 
        "stimulus": 3003, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UM"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UUUUM", 
        "correct": "UUM", 
        "incorrect": "UUU", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 1.084099681519451, 
        "stimulus": 2510, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "II"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IIII"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IIIIUUII", 
        "correct": "IIIIII", 
        "incorrect": "IIIUII", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 0.5204343948405317, 
        "stimulus": 2490, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UMMIU"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UUUUMMIU", 
        "correct": "UUMMIU", 
        "incorrect": "UUUMIU", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 0.9968623979438279, 
        "stimulus": 2593, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IMUMI"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IMUMIUU", 
        "correct": "IMUMI", 
        "incorrect": "IMUMU", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 1.0411156267197126, 
        "stimulus": 3190, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MMUM"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MMUMUU", 
        "correct": "MMUM", 
        "incorrect": "MMMU", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 0.6800735254367722, 
        "stimulus": 2737, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MM"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UUMM", 
        "correct": "MM", 
        "incorrect": "UM", 
        "length": 4, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 0.4892642534945744, 
        "stimulus": 2475, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IIU"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IIUUU", 
        "correct": "IIU", 
        "incorrect": "IUU", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 0.9108552505889073, 
        "stimulus": 3167, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        10, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        9, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        11, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        9, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UIMUMMIMI"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UIMUMMIMIUU", 
        "correct": "UIMUMMIMI", 
        "incorrect": "UIMUMMIMU", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 1.2247976325011303, 
        "stimulus": 2993, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MUU"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UUMUU", 
        "correct": "MUU", 
        "incorrect": "UUU", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 0.5679722898819567, 
        "stimulus": 2410, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MM"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MMUUU", 
        "correct": "MMU", 
        "incorrect": "MUU", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 0.6690306804948218, 
        "stimulus": 3007, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MU"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MUUUM", 
        "correct": "MUM", 
        "incorrect": "UUM", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 0.7425594713221071, 
        "stimulus": 2476, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MMU"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IUUMMU", 
        "correct": "IMMU", 
        "incorrect": "IUMU", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 0.5014690863293193, 
        "stimulus": 3208, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MUUUI"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MUUUIUUM", 
        "correct": "MUUUIM", 
        "incorrect": "MUUUIU", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 1.0776432585565225, 
        "stimulus": 3043, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IUMMI"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IUMMIUU", 
        "correct": "IUMMI", 
        "incorrect": "IUMMU", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 0.9458782358680576, 
        "stimulus": 3133, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UU"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UUUUI", 
        "correct": "UUI", 
        "incorrect": "UUU", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 0.8076198422519933, 
        "stimulus": 2543, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MIUUM"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IUM"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IUMUUMIUUM", 
        "correct": "IUMMIUUM", 
        "incorrect": "IUMUIUUM", 
        "length": 10, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 0.9146001468086172, 
        "stimulus": 2452, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MUUU", 
        "correct": "MU", 
        "incorrect": "UU", 
        "length": 4, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 0.8656620411877809, 
        "stimulus": 2388, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MUMII"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UUMUMII", 
        "correct": "MUMII", 
        "incorrect": "UUMII", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 1.1698530581278659, 
        "stimulus": 3013, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IU"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MI"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MIUUIU", 
        "correct": "MIIU", 
        "incorrect": "MUIU", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 0.543710753448685, 
        "stimulus": 3171, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        9, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UIIIUUI"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UIIIUUIUU", 
        "correct": "UIIIUUI", 
        "incorrect": "UIIIUUU", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 1.1341413593754954, 
        "stimulus": 2482, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MIMU"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IU"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IUUUMIMU", 
        "correct": "IUMIMU", 
        "incorrect": "IUUIMU", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 0.5726348953815393, 
        "stimulus": 2611, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UUIIM"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UUIIMUU", 
        "correct": "UUIIM", 
        "incorrect": "UUIIU", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 0.767305368957718, 
        "stimulus": 3266, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MUII"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MUUMUII", 
        "correct": "MMUII", 
        "incorrect": "UUUII", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 0.9796112690963257, 
        "stimulus": 3175, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MUI"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IUUMUI", 
        "correct": "IMUI", 
        "incorrect": "UUUI", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 0.704003823438294, 
        "stimulus": 2967, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MMIMUU"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MMIMUUUUI", 
        "correct": "MMIMUUI", 
        "incorrect": "MMIMUUU", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 1.1634744273166349, 
        "stimulus": 2941, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IMUM"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IUUIMUM", 
        "correct": "IIMUM", 
        "incorrect": "IUMUM", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 0.8077089145109004, 
        "stimulus": 2530, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IUIUI"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IUUIUIUI", 
        "correct": "IIUIUI", 
        "incorrect": "UUUIUI", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 0.8230425180857412, 
        "stimulus": 2563, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IIMMMI"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UII"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UIIUUIIMMMI", 
        "correct": "UIIIIMMMI", 
        "incorrect": "UIIUIMMMI", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 0.8801245029113779, 
        "stimulus": 2484, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UIMIIU"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UIMIIUUU", 
        "correct": "UIMIIU", 
        "incorrect": "UIMIUU", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 1.222452260931491, 
        "stimulus": 2374, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MUUU"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UMII"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UMIIUUMUUU", 
        "correct": "UMIIMUUU", 
        "incorrect": "UMIUMUUU", 
        "length": 10, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 0.7648983229452424, 
        "stimulus": 2642, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MIU"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IMMUI"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IMMUIUUMIU", 
        "correct": "IMMUIMIU", 
        "incorrect": "IMMUIUIU", 
        "length": 10, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 0.6150872132436344, 
        "stimulus": 2830, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IUU"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MUUIUU", 
        "correct": "MIUU", 
        "incorrect": "UUUU", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 0.5553758936089854, 
        "stimulus": 2903, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IUI"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UUIUI", 
        "correct": "IUI", 
        "incorrect": "UII", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 0.9842560167524684, 
        "stimulus": 2916, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IU"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IUUUM", 
        "correct": "IUM", 
        "incorrect": "UUM", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 0.9288552736947642, 
        "stimulus": 2560, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MM"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UUUMM", 
        "correct": "UMM", 
        "incorrect": "UUM", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 0.8412458460623256, 
        "stimulus": 2408, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UII"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "II"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IIUUUII", 
        "correct": "IIUII", 
        "incorrect": "IUUII", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 0.45764164240169386, 
        "stimulus": 2547, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IIM"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IIMUUM", 
        "correct": "IIMM", 
        "incorrect": "IIMU", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 0.6575093726680553, 
        "stimulus": 2994, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IUUU", 
        "correct": "IU", 
        "incorrect": "UU", 
        "length": 4, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 0.7791196430149214, 
        "stimulus": 2453, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UIMM"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UIMMUU", 
        "correct": "UIMM", 
        "incorrect": "UIMU", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 0.9635826547615215, 
        "stimulus": 2790, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UII"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UUUII", 
        "correct": "UII", 
        "incorrect": "UUI", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 0.9108552505889073, 
        "stimulus": 2467, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UI"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MU"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MUUUUI", 
        "correct": "MUUI", 
        "incorrect": "UUUI", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 0.6455164434886881, 
        "stimulus": 2649, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MIU"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MIUUU", 
        "correct": "MIU", 
        "incorrect": "MUU", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 0.8718328521418275, 
        "stimulus": 3233, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UMUMMI"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UMUMMIUU", 
        "correct": "UMUMMI", 
        "incorrect": "UMUMMU", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 1.213579712981267, 
        "stimulus": 2594, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MIIII"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MMU"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MMUUUMIIII", 
        "correct": "MMUMIIII", 
        "incorrect": "MMUUIIII", 
        "length": 10, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 0.9628340353810106, 
        "stimulus": 2550, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MU"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MIUIIU"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MIUIIUUUMU", 
        "correct": "MIUIIUMU", 
        "incorrect": "MIUIIUUU", 
        "length": 10, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 0.911723163614282, 
        "stimulus": 2956, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        9, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        10, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UIUUUUMU"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UIUUUUMUUU", 
        "correct": "UIUUUUMU", 
        "incorrect": "UIUUUUUU", 
        "length": 10, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 1.066265313115156, 
        "stimulus": 2370, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IUM"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UUIUM", 
        "correct": "IUM", 
        "incorrect": "UUM", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 0.6262246302449154, 
        "stimulus": 2935, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UUIM"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UUUUIM", 
        "correct": "UUIM", 
        "incorrect": "UUUM", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 0.865103844953492, 
        "stimulus": 3192, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        9, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MM"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IMUIMIU"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IMUIMIUUUMM", 
        "correct": "IMUIMIUMM", 
        "incorrect": "IMUIMIUUM", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 1.069537008092384, 
        "stimulus": 3099, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IUI"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IUIUU", 
        "correct": "IUI", 
        "incorrect": "IIU", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 0.9469251958871605, 
        "stimulus": 2605, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UUUM", 
        "correct": "UM", 
        "incorrect": "UU", 
        "length": 4, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 0.7791196430149214, 
        "stimulus": 2477, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MUM"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MUMUU", 
        "correct": "MUM", 
        "incorrect": "MMU", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 0.8608657493977935, 
        "stimulus": 2689, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MIM"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UUIUI"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UUIUIUUMIM", 
        "correct": "UUIUIMIM", 
        "incorrect": "UUIUIUIM", 
        "length": 10, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 0.8403246149950344, 
        "stimulus": 3197, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IIII"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IIM"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IIMUUIIII", 
        "correct": "IIMIIII", 
        "incorrect": "IIUIIII", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 0.7726682511523751, 
        "stimulus": 3165, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MIMMI"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MII"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MIIUUMIMMI", 
        "correct": "MIIMIMMI", 
        "incorrect": "MIIUIMMI", 
        "length": 10, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 0.8161197737484143, 
        "stimulus": 2644, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IM"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IUIUU"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IUIUUUUIM", 
        "correct": "IUIUUIM", 
        "incorrect": "IUIUUUM", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 1.036949318202041, 
        "stimulus": 2907, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UMMU"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UUUMMU", 
        "correct": "UMMU", 
        "incorrect": "UUMU", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 0.8675209058424781, 
        "stimulus": 3229, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IM"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MUUIM", 
        "correct": "MIM", 
        "incorrect": "MUM", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 0.5489854634510428, 
        "stimulus": 3256, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UII"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IUUUU"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IUUUUUUUII", 
        "correct": "IUUUUUII", 
        "incorrect": "UUUUUUII", 
        "length": 10, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 1.0656112747842623, 
        "stimulus": 2509, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MMUM"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MMUMUUU", 
        "correct": "MMUMU", 
        "incorrect": "MMUUM", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 0.7388898995786468, 
        "stimulus": 2740, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UU"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IM"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IMUUUU", 
        "correct": "IMUU", 
        "incorrect": "IUUU", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 0.9345672850150448, 
        "stimulus": 2954, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MMU"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IIMU"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IIMUUUMMU", 
        "correct": "IIMUMMU", 
        "incorrect": "IIUUMMU", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 0.6197377956882493, 
        "stimulus": 2942, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UIM"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IMMMM"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IMMMMUUUIM", 
        "correct": "IMMMMUIM", 
        "incorrect": "IMMMUUIM", 
        "length": 10, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 1.0221222484902333, 
        "stimulus": 3280, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MUI"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UUMUI", 
        "correct": "MUI", 
        "incorrect": "UUI", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 0.6262246302449154, 
        "stimulus": 2423, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IIMMII"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UM"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UMUUIIMMII", 
        "correct": "UMIIMMII", 
        "incorrect": "UMUIMMII", 
        "length": 10, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 0.8721659332613201, 
        "stimulus": 3330, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MMM"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MMMUU", 
        "correct": "MMM", 
        "incorrect": "MMU", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 0.36754934644718595, 
        "stimulus": 2678, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MM"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UMMM"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UMMMUUMM", 
        "correct": "UMMMMM", 
        "incorrect": "UMMUMM", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 0.5582725910016025, 
        "stimulus": 2557, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UIMI"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UUUIMI", 
        "correct": "UIMI", 
        "incorrect": "UUMI", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 1.0378598856787498, 
        "stimulus": 3259, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UUM"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UUUUM", 
        "correct": "UUM", 
        "incorrect": "UUU", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 1.0223573426124228, 
        "stimulus": 2947, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UU"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UMMM"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UMMMUUUU", 
        "correct": "UMMMUU", 
        "incorrect": "UMMUUU", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 1.0341781962154495, 
        "stimulus": 2706, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IU"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IUUUU", 
        "correct": "IUU", 
        "incorrect": "UUU", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 0.9734485355905388, 
        "stimulus": 2681, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        9, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UUMUIMI"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UUMUIMIUU", 
        "correct": "UUMUIMI", 
        "incorrect": "UUMUIMU", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 1.136757677011246, 
        "stimulus": 2937, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MUUII"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MM"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MMUUMUUII", 
        "correct": "MMMUUII", 
        "incorrect": "MUMUUII", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 0.9601250300102077, 
        "stimulus": 2552, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MIUI"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MUUMIUI", 
        "correct": "MMIUI", 
        "incorrect": "MUIUI", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 0.8056969089787321, 
        "stimulus": 2909, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UMUUI"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UMUUIUU", 
        "correct": "UMUUI", 
        "incorrect": "UMUUU", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 0.9655446904662323, 
        "stimulus": 3285, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MM"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UUU"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UUUUUMM", 
        "correct": "UUUMM", 
        "incorrect": "UUUUM", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 0.8381230852752102, 
        "stimulus": 2497, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        10, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        9, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        11, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        9, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MIMMUIUUI"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MIMMUIUUIUU", 
        "correct": "MIMMUIUUI", 
        "incorrect": "MIMMUIUUU", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 1.1603353671366194, 
        "stimulus": 2729, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MUIM"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IIM"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IIMUUMUIM", 
        "correct": "IIMMUIM", 
        "incorrect": "IIUMUIM", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 0.6116492311163861, 
        "stimulus": 3170, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MUIUMUM"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UM"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UMUUMUIUMUM", 
        "correct": "UMMUIUMUM", 
        "incorrect": "UMUUIUMUM", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 0.8187675228155267, 
        "stimulus": 2831, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UUI"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UUIUU", 
        "correct": "UUI", 
        "incorrect": "UUU", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 0.6262246302449154, 
        "stimulus": 2363, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IU"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UUUIU", 
        "correct": "UIU", 
        "incorrect": "UUU", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 0.8394386740705845, 
        "stimulus": 2698, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UMMMUM"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UMMMUMUU", 
        "correct": "UMMMUM", 
        "incorrect": "UMMMUU", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 1.1149426864876781, 
        "stimulus": 3103, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MMMMU"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MMMMUUUU", 
        "correct": "MMMMUU", 
        "incorrect": "MMMUUU", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 1.2598933697682784, 
        "stimulus": 3169, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IMI"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UUMI"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UUMIUUIMI", 
        "correct": "UUMIIMI", 
        "incorrect": "UUMUIMI", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 0.7473884653249224, 
        "stimulus": 3093, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "III"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IIIUUI", 
        "correct": "IIII", 
        "incorrect": "IIUI", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 0.7836848866781773, 
        "stimulus": 2397, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MI"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IUMU"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IUMUUUMI", 
        "correct": "IUMUMI", 
        "incorrect": "IUMUUI", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 0.9356323168551668, 
        "stimulus": 3194, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UUII"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UMMMI"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UMMMIUUUUII", 
        "correct": "UMMMIUUII", 
        "incorrect": "UMMMIUUUI", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 1.2069436827428208, 
        "stimulus": 3246, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IIMM"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MM"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MMUUIIMM", 
        "correct": "MMIIMM", 
        "incorrect": "MMUIMM", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 0.40911575557543584, 
        "stimulus": 2749, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MUMIIM"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MM"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MMUUMUMIIM", 
        "correct": "MMMUMIIM", 
        "incorrect": "MUMUMIIM", 
        "length": 10, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 0.7018147274920704, 
        "stimulus": 3064, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UI"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UIUUI", 
        "correct": "UII", 
        "incorrect": "UIU", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 0.5828806135042874, 
        "stimulus": 2940, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "III"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MM"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MMUUIII", 
        "correct": "MMIII", 
        "incorrect": "MUIII", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 0.7840940332055261, 
        "stimulus": 2657, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UUIM"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IIUU"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IIUUUUUUIM", 
        "correct": "IIUUUUIM", 
        "incorrect": "IUUUUUIM", 
        "length": 10, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 0.8304009552728939, 
        "stimulus": 3268, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UIUIMU"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IMU"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IMUUUUIUIMU", 
        "correct": "IMUUIUIMU", 
        "incorrect": "IUUUIUIMU", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 0.7799708992176628, 
        "stimulus": 3176, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UMUI"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UMUIUUM", 
        "correct": "UMUIM", 
        "incorrect": "UMUIU", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 0.8433101351052475, 
        "stimulus": 3076, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IMU"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UUIMU", 
        "correct": "IMU", 
        "incorrect": "UMU", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 0.7296453628256862, 
        "stimulus": 2376, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UMMMM"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UMMMMUU", 
        "correct": "UMMMM", 
        "incorrect": "UMMMU", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 0.2453419252637939, 
        "stimulus": 3070, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MU"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MUUUI", 
        "correct": "MUI", 
        "incorrect": "MUU", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 0.7679516974388002, 
        "stimulus": 3262, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IMIU"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UUIMIU", 
        "correct": "IMIU", 
        "incorrect": "UMIU", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 1.0521694826535095, 
        "stimulus": 3062, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MI"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UM"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UMUUMI", 
        "correct": "UMMI", 
        "incorrect": "UUUI", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 0.7711161750926319, 
        "stimulus": 3203, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MUMIMU"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MMM"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MMMUUMUMIMU", 
        "correct": "MMMMUMIMU", 
        "incorrect": "MMUMUMIMU", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 0.8067432026150305, 
        "stimulus": 2832, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MUM"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MI"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MIUUMUM", 
        "correct": "MIMUM", 
        "incorrect": "MUMUM", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 0.7451390429212683, 
        "stimulus": 3257, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MMMM"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MMMMUU", 
        "correct": "MMMM", 
        "incorrect": "MMMU", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 1.181112572122952, 
        "stimulus": 3284, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IIM"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UUIIM", 
        "correct": "IIM", 
        "incorrect": "UIM", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 0.9655709997470885, 
        "stimulus": 2675, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "III"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IIIUU", 
        "correct": "III", 
        "incorrect": "IIU", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 0.9842560167524684, 
        "stimulus": 2381, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IMMIUI"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IUUIMMIUI", 
        "correct": "IIMMIUI", 
        "incorrect": "IUMMIUI", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 0.9431998148903258, 
        "stimulus": 2719, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UM"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UMUUI", 
        "correct": "UMI", 
        "incorrect": "UMU", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 0.5828806135042874, 
        "stimulus": 2841, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        9, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        10, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IUMMIUIU"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IUMMIUIUUUU", 
        "correct": "IUMMIUIUU", 
        "incorrect": "IUMMIUUUU", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 1.421994234562333, 
        "stimulus": 3042, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MMIU"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MM"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MMUUMMIU", 
        "correct": "MMMMIU", 
        "incorrect": "MMUMIU", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 0.5428550267828536, 
        "stimulus": 2424, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UMIU"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MUUUMIU", 
        "correct": "MUMIU", 
        "incorrect": "MUUIU", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 0.9095728620948674, 
        "stimulus": 3107, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MM"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MMUU", 
        "correct": "MM", 
        "incorrect": "MU", 
        "length": 4, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 0.9428090415820634, 
        "stimulus": 2480, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        10, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        9, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        11, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        9, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IIUMIUUUM"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IIUMIUUUMUU", 
        "correct": "IIUMIUUUM", 
        "incorrect": "IIUMIUUUU", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 0.9956050840784871, 
        "stimulus": 2580, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MI"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MM"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MMUUMI", 
        "correct": "MMMI", 
        "incorrect": "MUMI", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 0.6348206737366319, 
        "stimulus": 2598, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UUMU"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MUI"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MUIUUUUMU", 
        "correct": "MUIUUMU", 
        "incorrect": "MUUUUMU", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 0.9029921155536753, 
        "stimulus": 2781, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UMM"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MUUUMM", 
        "correct": "MUMM", 
        "incorrect": "MUUM", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 0.8506784711875476, 
        "stimulus": 3333, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UIM"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IM"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IMUUUIM", 
        "correct": "IMUIM", 
        "incorrect": "IUUIM", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 0.657006921639599, 
        "stimulus": 2448, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MU"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UIIUI"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UIIUIUUMU", 
        "correct": "UIIUIMU", 
        "incorrect": "UIIUUUU", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 0.6242914238761145, 
        "stimulus": 2769, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        9, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MU"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IIUMUII"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IIUMUIIUUMU", 
        "correct": "IIUMUIIMU", 
        "incorrect": "IIUMUIUMU", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 1.0862322754378648, 
        "stimulus": 2825, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MIIIIM"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UUMIIIIM", 
        "correct": "MIIIIM", 
        "incorrect": "UIIIIM", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 1.3437203522501946, 
        "stimulus": 2556, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        11
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UIUUU"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UUUM"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UUUMUUUIUUU", 
        "correct": "UUUMUIUUU", 
        "incorrect": "UUUUUIUUU", 
        "length": 11, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 0.6634980057441089, 
        "stimulus": 2791, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        8, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        9, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        7, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "I"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UMMIUIU"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UMMIUIUUUI", 
        "correct": "UMMIUIUI", 
        "incorrect": "UMMIUIUU", 
        "length": 10, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 1.0133428517821002, 
        "stimulus": 3152, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MMU"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MMUUU", 
        "correct": "MMU", 
        "incorrect": "MUU", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 0.9108552505889073, 
        "stimulus": 2460, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IM"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UIM"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UIMUUIM", 
        "correct": "UIMIM", 
        "incorrect": "UIUIM", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 0.5415207580140448, 
        "stimulus": 2851, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IM"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MUU"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MUUUUIM", 
        "correct": "MUUIM", 
        "incorrect": "MUUUM", 
        "length": 7, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 1.0178590291994354, 
        "stimulus": 2816, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IUMU"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MU"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MUUUIUMU", 
        "correct": "MUIUMU", 
        "incorrect": "UUIUMU", 
        "length": 8, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 0.7758992694380616, 
        "stimulus": 3178, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        6, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MUMI"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UUUM"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UUUMUUMUMI", 
        "correct": "UUUMMUMI", 
        "incorrect": "UUUUUUMI", 
        "length": 10, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 0.6476344468589489, 
        "stimulus": 2799, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        5, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "UMI"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UMIUU", 
        "correct": "UMI", 
        "incorrect": "UMU", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 0.7113665205827001, 
        "stimulus": 2939, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        10
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        8
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IIUUIUUU"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        0
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": ""
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UUIIUUIUUU", 
        "correct": "IIUUIUUU", 
        "incorrect": "UIUUIUUU", 
        "length": 10, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 1.3015292821708204, 
        "stimulus": 2413, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        6
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "IUU"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "U"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "UUUIUU", 
        "correct": "UIUU", 
        "incorrect": "UUUU", 
        "length": 6, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 0.6800735254367722, 
        "stimulus": 2766, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        5
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        1, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MI"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        1
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "M"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "MUUMI", 
        "correct": "MMI", 
        "incorrect": "MUI", 
        "length": 5, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 0.6992031457885156, 
        "stimulus": 2521, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }, 
    {
        "alignment": [
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        3, 
                        4
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        3
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [], 
                "string": "U"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        4, 
                        9
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        2, 
                        7
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "MUIUM"
            }, 
            {
                "input": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "output": [
                    [
                        0, 
                        2
                    ]
                ], 
                "string": "II"
            }
        ], 
        "challenge": "IIUUMUIUM", 
        "correct": "IIMUIUM", 
        "incorrect": "IUMUIUM", 
        "length": 9, 
        "rule": "UU=e", 
        "score": 0.6514560209523704, 
        "stimulus": 2836, 
        "system": "MUI"
    }
]